<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Empire of Steel]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>lib\media\favicon.png</url><title>Empire of Steel</title><link/></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 01:06:07 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="lib\rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator/><item><title><![CDATA[July 27, 2176]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br><br>We drag Dr. No and a couple of his flunkies up to Mittens’ penthouse apartment. He’s spitting venom, absolutely furious, but that’s all he can do. It’s not too hard to get the information from him: his lab is in a recycling plant on the edge of Containment Zone 9, at the edge of the Tombs. They’re getting pressure from the Combinaught and the Joe Pox syndicates to share, but it hasn’t broken out into a full-fledged gang war. The deal was brokered via anonymous dropoff; they weren’t expecting the extra heat that showed up. The farm’s in the Southside NoGo, which is a war zone. It’s also highly suspected of being the HQ of the ADO Fifth—the Cybrid militia.<br>Moto’s got some information on the kidnap job. That the kids aren’t being ransomed is bad—it means there was some other reason they were kidnapped. That also means there are a limited number of locations they could be held: primarily other corpo campuses. These kids are inheritors; if it were proven another corp took them, that could mean an intercorporate war. In the chaos of the A-Spire, they dropped off the grid completely. No one’s touched their cred accounts or social media at all.<br>The only thing we know for sure is that there’s an agent with some hot information on <a data-href="Wutani" href="Wutani" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Wutani</a>, and the information is legit, because Wutani Internal Security’s after them. We can’t figure out why Wutani’s involved, but it’s not the first time we’ve run into Wutani sniffing around biotech. Moto goes into the Wutani corporate espionage data we picked up from the Moderns—it’s accounting data. Someone in Wutani’s committing accounting fraud; a guy named Emiliano Delacourt, a forensic accountant, was looking into it. The Moderns had an idea of who was committing the fraud. Dr. Lila Ortiz, the Moderns’ drug designer, might know; George Fyron, the manager of the Spire, might also know. Or, even better, we could call in a favor from Rico Silva, since he owes us for helping hold off the HouTex mercs.<br>Rico’s happy to put us in touch with Dr. Ortiz, via secure commlink in Obscura. The glands purchased were basal gland templates, which are used for more exotic genetics. Such as people who have been genetically improved. She’s designed a few very customized glands using basal templates; the client in question didn’t want the experience of the gland per se. They wanted the experience of the gland as felt by an individual. In other words, the basal templates are used to create single-user glands that can replicate the experience of one person to another. Bespoke dope. We can’t figure out an angle.<br>Rico’s able to send us surveillance footage of the kids getting taken. Lucky 13’s group goes down like the punks they are; the other group holds out longer, but eventually get taken out themselves. The kidnapper is Pumpkin Jack, a known serial killer, and someone who will take jobs for maintenance. Looks like his blades were loaded with a neurotoxin, enough to take the kids down but not kill them. He’s taking advantage of the chaos to get the kids… and he’s got help. Synths—old, out of date Wutani synths. It’s too much Wutani—it looks like someone inside Wutani skimming resources for a personal project. It looks like we’re going to have to pony up for the agent’s information. We can also poke around the Dollhouse, a clearing-house for synths and restricted chrome.<br>The agent wants hard cash, nothing traceable, that can be transferred elsewhere. Moto sets Obscura as the meet place; it’s a good place for anonymous meets. We settle in: Moto gets the message “Courier enroute; code FN.” The courier is only about 4 feet tall, with limbs of the wrong shape—because it’s a giant raven. His name is Full Nelson. Moto passes the money to FN, and FN passes back a protein drive. <br>The data dump: Project Trioseros is where the money’s going. It’s an attempt to create a drug to biomimic security systems. The project is completely outside the corporate structure except for one small funnel for money and logistics. The reports on the project are completely fake—most likely, this is a personal project using the corp for cover. The name on the project is David Franklin Clavell. And the agent who sold us the data—Emiliano Delacourt, the forensic accountant. The reason Delacourt’s running? A Wutani exec pursuing a personal project that’s been kept under the radar outranks a forensic accountant who might make the company look bad, even if it uncovers wrongdoing. They’ve found something in the failed experiments that destroys the mRNA in glands, referred to as ‘Ruiner’. It’s a virus that would essentially destroy glands. Attica narrows possible sites down to three: Black Helix, Neovana, and Null Street.<br>Neovana’s a neurocropolis, where the digitized deceased rest. Guarded by corporate monks. Black Helix is a reskinning lab. Null Street is 10 blocks of a “cogito-libertarian paradise”. Null Street is our likeliest contender—no one cares what goes on in there. They’ve got a flight of drones that keeps out satellite observation. They’re beyond paranoid. But, paradoxically, that might be our way in.<br>Mittens needs us to go into NoGo to the Paradise Line, very hush-hush, very sneak, and talk to Seven-Jim. Seven-Jim is the militant head of the Animal Technological Intervention Directive. Seven-Jim is going to raid the gland farm—but he plans to completely burn it out, whether or not they’re recoverable. She’d like us to try and talk Seven-Jim into a more nuanced approach, and fast…]]></description><link>operations\east-end-boys-&amp;-west-end-girls-part-1.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Operations/East End Boys &amp; West End Girls - Part 1.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 04:18:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[August 1, 2176]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br><br>The Butler has set us up with someone to help—she’s a synth, N3M-3515. She was built as an intelligent, self-directing synth that snapped when her favorite tech (that named her “Nemesis”) was killed by Weytani security. Moto gets into the synths’ cyberware and uncovers the security access protocols: door codes, locations of other synths in the building, maps, etc. Then he hacks their comms.<br>Silently, the team moves into position. Attica takes her target out first with a single strike. Spider and Firefox take out the second; this one’s tougher. Nemesis has trouble with the third one; despite her skill, it struggles. Graves comes in clutch and pops it from above. We take the stairs down; after Attica takes out the stairs guard, we split in two groups. Attica, Gloria and Spider head to the labs; Firefox, Nemesis and Graves go after Clavell.<br>The first two lab rooms are easy; the synths working here are non-combat models and fold beneath a threat of force.<br>Nemesis and Firefox walk into Clavell’s office. “Oh, an Amp! So exciting!” He looks at Nemesis. “I helped design your brain. In a way, I suppose I’m one of your fathers.” Nemesis activates her shock fists and Firefox mentally compels him to shut his mouth. Firefox lays it out for him: we’re here to take the children back, and he can either let them go or we can burn the whole place down with him in it. He starts to say that we can have the males, but it’s going to take some time to retrieve the women. (He’s perversely fascinated by the female form.) That’s when he twitches and a different voice comes from his throat: it’s Zaid, one of the girls we’re here to rescue. Somehow, Clavell has extracted the memory and personality engrams and injected it into himself. This is far beyond glands. He says she was irretrievably damaged by the process; Firefox hopes she can do something. "Moto comes on the network. “We’ve got movement; Clavell must have a panic button.”<br>Firefox threatens Clavell, and he’s thrilled by it. He’s getting high to stim; he’s neurodivergent. He’s so excited that we’re operators and threatening him. She offers him a weekly personalized experience—the “director’s cut”. It makes him come—and he claims to call off his synths. Perseus doesn’t stand down, however. Perseus is working for Clavell to maintain his individuality. He asks Nemesis if she’s working with us; she says yes. He tells us Clavell has a synthetic organ in his abdomen, accessible through an access port. It’s a biomod he uses to plug the organic data drives—the glands—into. To get Zaid out, Firefox will have to pull the data drive.<br>Meanwhile, four of the others are being decanted from the tubes; Strand’s in the scanner. She was in a simulation designed to provoke the maximum amount of hormone production, whiplashing her through multiple emotions. It’s based on a trite old piece of “cinema” based on the concept of rich old guys doing whatever they want to do without consequence. It turns out Clavell is the ideas guy, and the synths are the ones doing the actual work; they can even reverse the damage to Zaid.<br>Clavell surgically and chemically replaced his amygdala with a programmable emotive module, which he then set to ‘emotionless’. Presumably to reduce the signal-to-noise ratio for his “experiences.”<br>While the synths work to stabilize the kids and restore Zaid’s personality, while we call Strand in. He’s coldly furious. Perseus comes in a few moments later, wanting to make a deal. He wants a building—this one—for he and his people, while Clavell is hauled away. This is technically not against the law, but deeply frowned upon. We explain the situation to Strand, who wants to see Clavell’s operations completely destroyed.<br>Other information that Perseus has: Clavell’s lab failures have been passed on to Solberg, Douglass as part of the “cleanup” of Containment Zone 9. They’re highly exothermic—blow up under the least provocation. Clavell’s also been working with the Gouveia Syndicate, and Osric Kayne.<br>The new synth community is very grateful; they want to actually be a community, and would like to be friends and allies. They make the same offer to Strand. Strand, for his part, offers Perseus and some of the other synths jobs with Securitas should they need or want them. Strand points out that Perseus was being held hostage by Clavell’s ownership of the other synths, and holds no ill will. Strand will definitely be a useful contact in the future; he’s surprisingly ethical for a corp exec.<br>Attica kills Clavell without letting him wake up, and Firefox burns the body to ash.<br>“So,” Graves says. “With all that done, who’s our next target?”]]></description><link>operations\east-end-boys-&amp;-west-end-girls-part-6.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Operations/East End Boys &amp; West End Girls - Part 6.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 04:24:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Empire of Steel]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="Empire of Steel Banner.png" src="zresources\empire-of-steel-banner.png"><br><br>Caption
<img alt="Collision - The A-Spire Job.png" src="zresources\collision-the-a-spire-job.png"><br>
Current Adventure: Collision: The A-Spire Job
<br>
<br><a data-href="All Fall Down - Part 1" href="operations\all-fall-down-part-1.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">All Fall Down - Part 1</a>
<br><a data-href="All Fall Down - Part 2" href="operations\all-fall-down-part-2.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">All Fall Down - Part 2</a>
<br><a data-href="All Fall Down - Part 3" href="operations\all-fall-down-part-3.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">All Fall Down - Part 3</a>
<br><br>
<br><a data-href="Slings and Arrows - Part 1" href="operations\slings-and-arrows-part-1.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Slings and Arrows - Part 1</a>
<br><a data-href="Slings and Arrows - Part 2" href="operations\slings-and-arrows-part-2.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Slings and Arrows - Part 2</a>
<br><a data-href="Slings and Arrows - Part 3" href="operations\slings-and-arrows-part-3.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Slings and Arrows - Part 3</a>
<br><br>
<br><a data-href="Collision - Part 1" href="operations\collision-part-1.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Collision - Part 1</a>
<br><a data-href="Collision - Part 2" href="operations\collision-part-2.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Collision - Part 2</a>
<br><a data-href="Collision - Part 3" href="operations\collision-part-3.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Collision - Part 3</a>
<br><a data-href="Collision - Part 4" href="operations\collision-part-4.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Collision - Part 4</a>
<br><a data-href="Collision - Part 5" href="operations\collision-part-5.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Collision - Part 5</a>
<br><a data-href="Collision - Part 6" href="operations\collision-part-6.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Collision - Part 6</a>
<br><a data-href="Collision - Part 7" href="operations\collision-part-7.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Collision - Part 7</a>
<br><br>
<br><a data-href="Collision - The A-Spire Job - Part 1" href="operations\collision-the-a-spire-job-part-1.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Collision - The A-Spire Job - Part 1</a>
<br><a data-href="Collision - The A-Spire Job - Part 2" href="operations\collision-the-a-spire-job-part-2.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Collision - The A-Spire Job - Part 2</a>
<br><a data-href="Collision - The A-Spire Job - Part 3" href="operations\collision-the-a-spire-job-part-3.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Collision - The A-Spire Job - Part 3</a>
<br><a data-href="Collision - The A-Spire Job - Part 4" href="operations\collision-the-a-spire-job-part-4.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Collision - The A-Spire Job - Part 4</a>
<br><a data-href="Collision - The A-Spire Job - Part 5" href="operations\collision-the-a-spire-job-part-5.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Collision - The A-Spire Job - Part 5</a>
<br><br>
<br><a data-href="East End Boys &amp; West End Girls - Part 1" href="operations\east-end-boys-&amp;-west-end-girls-part-1.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">East End Boys &amp; West End Girls - Part 1</a>
<br><a data-href="East End Boys &amp; West End Girls - Part 2" href="operations\east-end-boys-&amp;-west-end-girls-part-2.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">East End Boys &amp; West End Girls - Part 2</a>
<br><a data-href="East End Boys &amp; West End Girls - Part 3" href="operations\east-end-boys-&amp;-west-end-girls-part-3.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">East End Boys &amp; West End Girls - Part 3</a>
<br><a data-href="East End Boys &amp; West End Girls - Part 4" href="operations\east-end-boys-&amp;-west-end-girls-part-4.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">East End Boys &amp; West End Girls - Part 4</a>
<br><a data-href="East End Boys &amp; West End Girls - Part 5" href="operations\east-end-boys-&amp;-west-end-girls-part-5.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">East End Boys &amp; West End Girls - Part 5</a>
<br><a data-href="East End Boys &amp; West End Girls - Part 6" href="operations\east-end-boys-&amp;-west-end-girls-part-6.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">East End Boys &amp; West End Girls - Part 6</a>
<br><br><br><br><br>
<br>Emergency cash vault: 29.5K
<br>30k of street drugs, maker tools, and corpo industrial secrets—a dossier on one <a data-href="Dr. Su Xinyi Zheng" href="people\dr.-su-xinyi-zheng.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dr. Su Xinyi Zheng</a>.
<br>A stash behind <a data-href="Violator" href="places\violator.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Violator</a>:  some collectibles, a couple crates of current-gen Colonial-issue MREs (better rats than a lot of people eat right now). Below the container is a highly-shielded secondary container that’s set up as a small safe-house, including a clone tank.
<br>Identities of secret corporate moles in Watanabe-Maille World Aerospace 
<br>Blackmail material on an employee working for the Panzers inside McKesson Corporation 
<br>50k in identities of secret corporate moles in Weytani
<br>$75k Wu - to get Zina and Artemis off-planet
<br>Negotiable property deeds
<br>$25k in brand-new cyberware - to Zina
<br>Redding Tech 'Icepick' Cyberdeck - to Moto
<br>40 k in:

<br>Several hidden cache locations for the Moderns
<br>Information on corporate moles working for Waring-Erikson Technology Group, Nubotica, and Fuji
<br>A shipment of extremely fashionable clothing designs meant for the Moderns' joytoys
<br>Corporate industrial secrets from Weytani and Watanabe-Maille World Aerospace.


<br>40 k in:

<br>Employee-stolen products hidden away
<br>Secret cache locations
<br>Negotible deeds of ownership
<br>Unregistered mint in box cyberware


<br><br><br><br>]]></description><link>index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Index.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 04:16:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="zresources\empire-of-steel-banner.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="zresources\empire-of-steel-banner.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[July 28, 2176]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br>We need to start with the major players on Null Street.<br>Angelino Schäfer<br>
<br>Founder of Null Street
<br>Live-and-let-live libertarian
<br>Owns the majority of the property in Null Street
<br>Libertarian idealist with a careful nature
<br>Can’t lie for shit
<br>Walt Angus<br>
<br>Null Street’s lawyer
<br>Well known for knowing his shit, never backing down
<br>Seems on-board with Schaffer’s ideology
<br>Vigorously foul-mouthed, even in court
<br>Algis Solberg<br>
<br>Will argue with anyone
<br>Has a podcast: the Devil’s Advocate
<br>Has the most annoying laugh in the world, like a hyena in a higher register
<br>Sodia Douglass<br>
<br>Owns a number of wineries and distilleries (semi-illegal due to explody risk)
<br>Tends to buck the other 5 majority players
<br>Fixture at parties in AusTex because she brings the booze
<br>Shameless flirt
<br>Maina McFarland<br>
<br>AMP
<br>AMP outreach/spiritual center of Null Street
<br>Uses her massive wealth to help other people, with an almost religious zeal
<br>Spiritual framework: human body is divine; anything you do to enhance or improve it is holy service
<br>Gets snippy to downright mean when people question that
<br>Cyberpath; has both AMP abilities and cyberware
<br>Muireann Waller<br>
<br>In charge of Null Street’s infrastructure
<br>Tends to ride to the rescue when things get messed up (fairly frequently)
<br>Not one for argument; she just gets things done
<br>Moto gets into the high-security files, sealed by <a data-href="Osric Kayne" href="people\osric-kayne.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Osric Kayne</a>. Turns out that the Containment Zone, where there was a big industrial accident. Multiple city blocks rendered (allegedly) uninhabitable. Involved an AMP research lab. Weird shit in there is nothing unusual. The people involved in the highly illegal lab that exploded: Solberg, Douglass, and Waller. (Waller was bought out in a hostile takeover not long before the accident, but assuredly knows exactly what caused it.) It was all previously property of Angelino Schäfer. <br>In the other room, Graves is arguing with someone on his phone. It’s a contact of his—doesn’t seem to want to take no for an answer. His contact wants a face-to-face to “explain things”—she’s a journalist that doesn’t take business terribly seriously, and is ignoring that she’d be expecting him/us to burn another group of operators and a valuable fixer. Her concern is adjacent to Zero’s job: There’s “burners” in the Containment Zone that are being dumped off by a group of mercs, running up to and into buildings, and exploding. A group called the Rust is working the job, and they’re a good, solid group. We decide to hear her out, and then advise Zero what’s going on, see how he wants to handle it.<br>The meeting takes place at the <a data-href="Neon Lotus" href="places\neon-lotus.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Neon Lotus</a>. We’re escorted to a middle-level conference room, where two people are waiting. One is Trevor Hammacher; the other is Brandy Graves. Aidan’s sister. Trevor is the serious one.<br>The Rust is busy protecting <a data-href="Lady V" href="people\lady-v.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Lady V</a>’s clinic. Problem is, Wutani’s sniffing around. Specifically, Wutani Internal Security. Janice Egorva, who most recently was hunting down Emeliano Delacourt (the forensic accountant). Brandy and Trevor were looped in because they’re performing their own investigation into the burners; the Rust doesn’t have the manpower to conduct the investigation, so they’re subcontracting. It’s a one-night, 45k job. Brandy has some hacked invites to a party for Míra Olaya Süss, a Wutani exec, celebrating Wutani’s new line of synths; she just wants us to mingle spread some tiny bio-tech bugs.<br>Firefox finds a date: Galina Zając, Kerensky-Armiger Services Corporation. She’s older than she looks; having retired from the battlefield, she’s turned to slaughtering opponents in the boardroom.<br>Abimbola Arendse, Securitas, is Süss’s bodyguard, on permanent contract. Firefox gets a lot more information on the attendees: it’s an international, multi-corporate event. Moto gets the floor plans. Attica does some pre-party recon at the villa: the outer security is pretty standard. Cameras, stun mesh, monowire over glass. There’s guards on site, carrying combi-weapons (combination lethal/nonlethal/anti-drone). It’s the most comfortable-looking fortress she’s ever seen. The inner perimeter is lower-security, but does have transmitters to fuck people’s chrome and install malware. No internal cameras; they depend on floaters. They’re not using multiple security groups; all the security arrangements go through Securitas. Heavy security is provided by Tiger response suits—fast, mobile, exceedingly well-armed.<br>Attica’s infiltrated the staff. The head of security’s moving about, checking everything out via her AR rig. Attica notices someone not quite right: someone heavily enhanced, possibly full-synthetic. She’s carrying a sword of orbital steel with a monomolecular edge, and she’s keeping it hidden. Attica sends the image to Moto; they’re a classified service contractor, listed not by name but by function. “Butler”. Their current charge is Nathaniel Bancroft Jamieson the Eighth, on behalf of Dell Multi-Corporation. AKA “Lucky 13”.<br>The attendees are the glitterati of half a dozen companies. Süss starts off by showing off their latest synth: designed for assassination and terror operations, it can be loaded with personality profiles that can make it not even aware it’s a synth. Süss also apologizes that Clavell isn’t there; he’s unavoidably detained by other business. The Reaper 17 is currently in field trials—Pumpkin Jack.]]></description><link>operations\east-end-boys-&amp;-west-end-girls-part-2.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Operations/East End Boys &amp; West End Girls - Part 2.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 01:52:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[July 29, 2176]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br><br>This is one of those parties that, despite allegedly being for “networking”, is really just there for rich people to get their freak on. Outside, Calamity notices a peculiar ripple in the sky above the house… she spots a ship hovering above the roof. Looks like a Jacana-class dropship running a stealth package. It’s a Securitas ship. We have George keep an eye on it. Meanwhile, we’re stashing cameras. Gloria gets one in the cabana area, then tries for the exercise room. She has to divert before she’s spotted by security.<br>Galina, Firefox’s date, does not sugarcoat things—she’s talking about kill counts and casualties, and is really looking to make the sale. Firefox can’t quite hide her interest in what’s going on, and Galina drags her off to the library for a little tete-a-tete. Fortunately, Firefox is able to deflect Galina’s interest; they spend some time getting intimate.<br>Xzavier and Mudiwa are having an intense conversation about cats; this appears to piss off Oni Takamura, who rolls up on Huỳnh. <br>She draws him into an intense exchange. Oni’s got a transport job, and Huỳnh’s lost control of some raiders along the route she needs to travel. She’s transporting waste from Containment Zone 9 to Selma, and the contract she’s put out for additional guards hasn’t been filled. Huỳnh tries to hit on her, and she rebuffs him with a comment about his co-worker; he retorts that he knows about her affairs.<br>Moto mentions something odd about the dropship; it’s heavily scanning areas of the building that should be covered by household sensors. Attica opines that it’s setting up for a kidnap or assassination; they haven’t moved yet, likely because the target isn’t here yet. There’s a possibility this is a move by Securitas to snatch Clavell; unfortunately for them, Suss claimed he wasn’t going to be there. Securitas may decide to go after Wynter, the Wutani IntSec CEO, as a fall-back. This probably isn’t a sanctioned Securitas operation.<br>Outside, Calamity and Moto spot three Wutani armored vehicles rolling up the drive. They’re IntSec, armed and armored with high-end gear. Attica ghosts over to the office and drops a bug there without being noticed; upstairs, Firefox isn’t so lucky. She trips on something. A spy-eye bobbles past her, apparently uncaring, but a moment later, a purple-haired girl in yellow glasses steps into the room. “Who the hell are you?” Firefox isn’t picking up thoughts off of the girl. “You need to leave. This is my area, and I’m waiting for someone.” Firefox manages to talk her way out; on her way out, she realizes that the girl is a high-end synth body double. She’s got that corpo-kiddy slumming look. This is part of Securitas’ trap—trying to draw Clavell out. <br>Firefox brings the security maneuvering to Galina’s attention. The KASC exec is not happy. She’s heading downstairs when the Securitas dropship drops cloak. Chaos erupts. The first two Wutani vehicles go right through the gate, and Egorva storms in with a whole group of synths. Securitas personnel are ordered to go up against the wall; everyone else is ordered to leave immediately. Outside, Calamity and Moto are ordered to show their IDs; Moto has to do some fancy hacking to make their credentials look more solid. After a thorough check, the synth returns the ID and advises that we leave now, as there’s about to be trouble.<br>We get out of there just as the yelling starts.<br>Back at the Neon Lotus, Brandy starts going through the footage. We get some good information out of it.<br>Takamura continues to chew out Huỳnh. She’s pissed about the rivalry between HouTex and Austex. He keeps claiming he’s not interfering with her business; she’s just collateral damage, and they’ll compensate her for that. “Look, if you want to move the waste, I can tell you who’s keeping it from being moved. <a data-href="Osric Kayne" href="people\osric-kayne.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Osric Kayne</a>. He’s working with the Combinaughts, who say they can dispose of the waste without it being moved to Selma.” Osric’s in it up to his neck, Detective Kennedy is his go-between, and the “missing executive” tonight was avoiding IntSec’s attention, because he went to Space City and bought some “interesting” equipment on his personal credit line.”<br>Oren Strand, a Securitas exec, is one of the execs that Wutani’s people is holding. He admits this was a personal action, and tells Egorva and Wynter that if they don’t return the kids unharmed, he’ll take the evidence he has to the Securitas board and call for a full corpo war.]]></description><link>operations\east-end-boys-&amp;-west-end-girls-part-3.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Operations/East End Boys &amp; West End Girls - Part 3.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 01:52:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[July 30, 2176]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br>Strand seems to be a father who actually cares, far beyond what’s usual for corporate families. Certainly it says something that he’s willing to start a corporate war over his kid. That might mean someone we can deal with. We have a great deal of information that we don’t have the leverage to use; he needs someone discreet to go in and get the children out without starting a war. We might be able to negotiate a quid pro quo. <br>Firefox puts in the call—Strand’s agent is back to us within 15 minutes, wanting a face-to-face. He suggests a protein farm in the Outlaw—an unusual location for a corpo to suggest. When we arrive, we notice that the security is absolutely insane; it’s likely this is a discreet safe house. <br>Strand knows more about the history of glanding—it was a military project from the early 21st century that fell into the hands of terrorists, and then was abandoned until 50 years ago. He adds that once upon a time, Clavell was a brilliant manager, valued for his ability to see trends. He’s made Wutani a lot of money in some of their smaller product lines, including enhanced animals. (Strand looks angry at this.) Disposable animals. He’s fascinated with the writings of a questionable French philosopher—de Sade—and had animals engineered to replicate works like the 100 Days of Sodom.<br>Strand has a habit of playing with a specific ring—it’s a polyamory ring. Three layers, one of them black. One of his spouses died, and no one else has been brought into the polycule. The rings also include their genomes. Both wives are clones. He’s a pragmatic man, but utterly devoted to his family. <br>Strand has left a bottle of bioengineered dandruff shampoo, distributed by a holding company based out of the Brasilian Amazonas called the Gouveia Syndicate, mostly smugglers. The biomedical company that makes this shampoo is several levels down. When Kes scans the code, on the shampoo, there’s a shipping label. The name is Elpídio Eurico Gouveia, but the address matches <a data-href="Osric Kayne" href="people\osric-kayne.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Osric Kayne</a>.<br>Infobox

<img alt="null street.png" src="lib\media\null-street.png">
<br>Null Street is nice and straight, neatly set out with little suburbs around it. They have a lot of comms; most likely, they’re laundering money through Algerian satellites. The area’s surrounded by drones, and all the inhabitants are heavily armed. They don’t have a problem with us carrying weapons, either; they would never interfere with the right of a citizen to carry as many weapons as they want. They also have a lot of biomass reactors—easy, clean disposal of anything, or anyone, that might go wrong.<br>The northern triangle is where the founders live; the middle blocks are general residential housing, and the southern area is commercial. In the southeast corner is an old corpo office building; quite the antique. When it was first built, it was an apartment complex called the Goodwin. It was one of the first proto-arcologies, part of the 21st century gentrification. It also had a lot of neo-hippy facilities inside that got cultish after the Incident; they were raided in the late 21st by both the authorities and the Church for trying to infect others with AMP. Clavell’s got a 20-year lease on the Goodwin.<br>There’s cameras and man-traps on the bottom level, including a security contingent of a half-dozen men. There’s an AV pad on the roof. The top two floors and the roof are the active parts of the building; there’s four floors worth of dead space below. Equipment’s been moved onto the top floors by AV. The security’s either ex-military or corporate military, professional but not elite. Two in the lobby, one on either side, two at the delivery dock. They probably have reinforcements, but it would take some time. Thermal indicates a big power draw on the fifth floor and nothing on the sixth.<br>We consider possible infiltration options, but ultimately, we realize we need to do a second round of recon to finalize our plans…]]></description><link>operations\east-end-boys-&amp;-west-end-girls-part-4.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Operations/East End Boys &amp; West End Girls - Part 4.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 02:58:58 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\null-street.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\null-street.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[August 1, 2176]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br><br>We get set up in an empty building near the Goodwin Building; it’s centrally located, and abandoned save for construction robots and a cursory security patrol.  Firefox does a passive telepathic scan of the building—the lower floors aren’t entirely abandoned, but the fifth floor is absolutely seething with an amount of pleasure that borders on agony.<br>We have our monitoring set up, and quickly spot Butler casing the area. She’s clearly here for Lucky 13. We also see something outside of the building: a man-sized shimmer of thermoptic camo. Someone’s crawling around on the outside of the building; the “butler” does a good job of avoiding it. We maintain surveillance on it, and finally realize it’s the Reaper. Pumpkin Jack.<br>Firefox gives Butler a psychic ping, and she climbs the walls to visit us. We agree to work together to get the kids out; we need to do it soon, quick, and quiet. We decide to go in from the top, and it’s on.<br>We zipline over to the Goodwin Building’s roof. There’s two synths on the top.]]></description><link>operations\east-end-boys-&amp;-west-end-girls-part-5.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Operations/East End Boys &amp; West End Girls - Part 5.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 01:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Osric Kayne]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

<img alt="cover hmed" src="lib\media\osric-kayne.png"><br>
Corrupt Politician
<br>Member of the <a data-href="AusTex City Development Council" href="AusTex City Development Council" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">AusTex City Development Council</a>. <br>
<br>Provided the Panzers the gear as part of an unholy union between <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Koizumi Aerospace Corporation" data-href="Koizumi Aerospace Corporation" href="factions\koizumi-aerospace-corporation.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Koizumi Aerospace</a> and AusTex. 
<br>Planned to have the Panzers clear everyone out to make room for a Koizumi manufacturing plant—specifically, one across from the Tesla Gigafactory. 
<br>Real name: Elpídio Eurico Gouveia
]]></description><link>people\osric-kayne.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">People/Osric Kayne.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 02:13:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\osric-kayne.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\osric-kayne.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lady V]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

“img.png” could not be found.<br>
Extra Info
<br>Well known cyberdoc. Used to be involved in some serious gangoon activity. Respected.<br>She’s got a burner that hasn’t developed yet under sedation; she’s trying to keep it quiet. Weytani’s goons have been sniffing around. ]]></description><link>people\lady-v.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">People/Lady V.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 01:41:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Neon Lotus]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

“img.png” could not be found.<br>
Extra Info
<br>A flowtel on Lake Travis. It’s a members-only building, though it’s possible to get a day pass through money, blackmail or invite. The building is a Japanese-themed version of the Spire, and is probably owned by the Yakuza. The day pass includes privacy and anonymity.]]></description><link>places\neon-lotus.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Places/Neon Lotus.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 01:36:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cascadia Pro-Cop]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>They like to give the impression of being “Officer Friendly”.<br><img alt="Bryker Woods.png" src="lib\media\bryker-woods.png">]]></description><link>factions\cascadia-pro-cop.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Factions/Cascadia Pro-Cop.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 01:28:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\bryker-woods.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\bryker-woods.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Panzer Hammers]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Neo-Nazis with light tanks. They’re a chromer gang—heavy on the cyberware—and their deepest desire is to shed the flesh and become one with one of their panzers.<br><br>]]></description><link>factions\panzer-hammers.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Factions/Panzer Hammers.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 01:28:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Spirit Moderns]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>They’re the ones currently holding control over <a data-href="Barton Springs" href="Barton Springs" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Barton Springs</a>, the major water source for the metroplex.<br>They also have a tendency to break their toys.<br><br>]]></description><link>factions\spirit-moderns.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Factions/Spirit Moderns.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 01:27:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weytani]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 ]]></description><link>factions\weytani.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Factions/Weytani.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 02:42:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[July 2, 2176]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br><br>There’s nothing good about carnivals, and even less about burned-out, abandoned carnivals. So it makes sense that creepy cultists are going to be using this as a meet point.<br>We get the low-down on the flash team. They’re working for Misha Fernandez of <a data-href="The Circuit" href="factions\the-circuit.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Circuit</a>, put together by the (allegedly) ex-corpo fixer <a data-href="Tanit Saad" href="people\tanit-saad.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Tanit Saad</a>.<br>
<br>No one likes working with Emma Baurrfau; she’s wired to the gills with speedware and is a psycho razorgirl
<br>Jules Fillion is considered one of the toughest operators in the AusTex area; he just doesn’t die
<br>Terminal Conflict has been rumored to have blown the last couple decking jobs they’ve taken, for reasons unknown
<br>Eymeric Richara has an unfortunate street name—Jank—due to the fact that his chrome is janky. They are the relative of someone fairly high in the criminal scheme of things in AusTex proper
<br>Catrine Duchamp is a face, not a fixer, and she’s in debt due to a very expensive drug habit
<br>The thing they have in common is: they’re all financially desperate. <br>There’s a run-down motel outside the carnival; looks like someone’s set up there. We do some investigation into which crew’s set up. Annika sends out a telepathic probe… and senses bio-roids. Those are the buyers.<br>George goes out to recon the carnival itself, and finds the sellers. Duchamp’s set up on the ferris wheel in a sniping position, packing some serious heat. Several of the others are on monobikes. We decide the safest bet is to try to warn the sellers; if we can get them on our side, taking down the bio-roids will be a lot easier.<br>Jules is the one taking point for the sellers, though it’s clear he’s on the comms with someone else. Annika does the negotiating on our end—fortunately, nobody sane likes bio-roids, and we point out that just because we’re not getting a payout doesn’t mean we don’t have a reason to go after those things. They invite us in, and we get set up near the coaster just a few moments before the buyer shows up.<br>In his van full of bio-roids.<br>We recognize the driver: <a data-href="Jan de Ven" href="people\jan-de-ven.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Jan de Ven</a>. She starts to talk, starts to show a credvault—and then she recognizes us. And her eyes flicker.<br>Attika leaps into action; in an instant she has Jan de Ven on the ground unconscious. The client, Fernandez, pulls out in a panic; we ignore her. A vehicle drops down from the omnipresent cloud cover—it’s a Weytani AV. It circles the area, but doesn’t as yet do anything. And then, the bio-roids—no longer under de Ven’s control—pour out of the van. They’re armed with all sorts of interesting weapons, and smart enough to take at least partial cover. They’re still moving under direction; it looks like de Ven wasn’t the primary controller. Could be one of the bio-roids itself, or possibly someone in the Weytani ‘craft.<br>Atop the ferris wheel, Catrina cuts loose with the M24; she’s blasting holes in the ‘roids in a combination of suppression and area effect. Annika stares at Flamethrower ‘Roid… and sets him on fire. The tanks of his flamethrower go boom. Several of the bio-roids collapse, dead. Two more are incapacitated. At that point, the AV slams down to the ground behind the ‘roids. Two of the bio-roids are still up; one turns and runs for the fence, apparently having more brains than his buddies. Then he runs for Gloria’s van.<br>Emma blasts the other remaining bio-roid into chunky salsa, and the AV disgorges a black-clad WeYu EEL team. Meanwhile, Gloria’s not happy that someone’s going after her van, and corpsifies him with a three-round burst. Inside Fernandez’ van, Misha and Saad are having some sort of argument. Spider dashes to the van, knocks on the windows with her claws, and says, “Play nicely, my friends?” The two women are definitely not playing nicely, so Spider yanks Saad out of the van and slams her down on the ground to the sound of Fernandez screaming “Fucking puta bitch!” after Saad. She hops out of the van, pointing her gun right at Tanit’s face. “Fucking sell me out to WeYu? You’re gonna fuckin’ die.”]]></description><link>operations\collision-part-6.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Operations/Collision - Part 6.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 01:09:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[July 4, 2176]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br><br>All hell is breaking loose. The Church is breaking in like they’re on some sort of crusade. Father László is yelling for calm; Firefox’s fans are having none of it. Vox D is shouting “Down with the Church” and putting music behind.<br>Over the PA, we hear Darius’s voice: “Attention all patrons: we’re being joined by the Church of the Cyberpapacy!”<br>László is shouting, “TURN AWAY FROM SIN! TURN AWAY FROM THE MACHINATIONS OF THE DEVIL!!!”<br>And then there’s the AI, the big blue hologram hovering in the air: I AM PROMETHEUS. I AM THE VOICE OF SECTOR CONTROL. THE CHURCH—THE CYBERPAPACY—IS LYING TO YOU.<br>László doesn’t like that; he signals to the jack-priests, who pull out sophisticated cyberdecks to try to get rid of it. Outside, the assault craft whine as the Church sends their pods in to seize control of the complex. Prometheus retaliates against the jack-priests; they scream and start seizing as if someone’s overloaded their implants. FATHER LÁSZLÓ, LET US SPEAK. GOD TO VERY SMALL MAN.<br>Outside, Attica grabs Crasher by the throat. “Who the hell was your target?” She threatens to dangle him out the hole he just made, and he starts to crack. He was forced to shoot—the person who hired him threatened to shut him completely down. We get the rest out of him by offering to remove the killswitch.<br>Crasher doesn’t know who hired him—describes him as “some woman”. By his description, it was Algol, Darius’ new head of security. Why she would want to shoot whoever he shot—he only had targeting information. George comes up to do a scan, and says, “I know who he shot… it’s Darius.”<br>Inside, Prometheus continues. I BELIEVE THAT FATHER LÁSZLÓ KNOWS THE CHURCH’S SECRET. DO YOU WISH TO TELL THEM, OR SHALL I?<br>László shrieks, “You can’t! You cannot! You must not!”<br>DO YOU NOT BELIEVE THE TRUTH IN THE MACHINE? AM I NOT THE VERY INCEPTION OF YOUR GOD?<br>The bodyguards of the downed jack-priests start firing indiscriminately at the hologram. Two of them run right past Spider; she moves fluidly and takes them down to prevent them from shooting into the crowd. Similarly, Gloria fires on another bodyguard, incapacitating them. Kes goes after a fourth; she can’t get through his armor. He howls, “HERETIC!” and gets a hit in on her. Calamity spins and cuts loose with her shotgun, taking out one of a pair; his buddy fires off a short burst and nails Calamity right back.<br>Outside, Graves is picking up some other speech, competing with the Church’s propaganda stream. It’s Reality Black; she’s saying some fairly standard violent jackass rhetoric—in the name of the workers, they’re going to liberate AusTex. They’re in the process of adding Reagent 18 to the water supply. Reagent 18 is a deadly neurotoxin—but it makes people violent and crazy before they die, or if they get a nonlethal dose. It’s a progressive condition with no cure. It’s the stuff that got sailed into New York Harbor, which was the reason they had to wall off Manhattan and several of the boroughs.<br>Plex security is putting people on the ground, and it’s about to turn into an all-out war between the Moderns and the Church, with Reality Black taking advantage of the chaos to poison the water supply.<br>Prometheus is arguing with someone—likely Reality Black. NO. YOU WILL NOT. THIS IS NOT WHAT WE AGREED ON. SHUTTING OFF WATER CONTROLS. <br>We’ve got to get to the water treatment plant; with the computer controls shut off, Black will need to access the water treatment plant directly. Moto gets us an underground route to avoid the war zone topside’s turned into so we can haul ass and try to intercept.<br>As we make our way through the tunnels, George reports a problem. There’s a Spire security patrol on the other side of the channel; if there’s a coup going on, no telling whose side they’re on. “Spread out, goddamnit! Find them!” Attica and Firefox work together to create a distraction, and dash past the guards into an industrial area. There’s another group farther on—members of the <a data-href="Texas Syndicate" href="factions\texas-syndicate.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Texas Syndicate</a>. They’re carrying military duffels.<br>We opt to continue the stealth approach: Graves moves up; one of the goons sees something, but Annika clouds his mind. Graves takes him down with a single suppressed pistol shot. Attica ghosts up and knifes her target in the neck, then throws his dead body over a ledge. Annika ceiling-crawls and takes out the third. Graves finds an improvised explosive and calls Kes to take a look—it’s not armed. It’s there to hamper pursuit or mess up the machinery, but we moved too fast. It’s unstable, and Kes doesn’t want to mess with it.<br>One of the hazmat guys is coming toward the door; we position ourselves. When the door opens, we move, and it’s a complete surprise. Gloria hits the lead hazmat guy with a 3-round burst, but the suit soaks up most of the damage. Spider jumps in and takes out the nearest gunman. Graves leaps in, uses the hazmat guy for cover, and hazmat guy throws off his aim. In a flurry of gunfire, Calamity and Kes manage to take down another Syndicate op. But there’s 2 more in the security office…]]></description><link>operations\collision-the-a-spire-job-part-4.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Operations/Collision - The A-Spire Job - Part 4.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 23:18:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[July 4, 2176]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br><br>Behind us, Moto comes racing in; he’s got himself an upgraded drone! Gloria’s rifle roars, and another gunman falls. A Syndicate guy pops out of one of the corridor between us and the Modern patrol that followed Moto down; caught between two warring forces, he panics and runs. The patrol’s led by Rico Silva, one of the Modern’s smugglers; he recognizes us as part of Annika’s band, and starts yelling for us to get out of the way. Firefox lets him know what’s going on, and that we came down to help.<br>Four dudes drop in—Firefox spots them. They’re above us; they crawled along the pipes, and they sparkle. They’re from an outfit called KBR: Kellogg-Brown Resources. Another HouTex PMC. Moto dodges out of their line of fire and lets loose his new hound drone, Lycos. Its submachine gun spits lead at the lead merc, but doesn’t take him down. Two of the remaining Syndicate guys take potshots at Gloria and Attica, but miss. Rico moves up, mag-dumping his carbine against the intruders, shredding three of them. The leading merc, having seen the rest of his squad go down, turns and runs. <br>We keep one of the Syndicate mooks alive to interrogate. He plays a tough guy, but Annika is able to get into his head without much of a problem. The Syndicate’s been paid a lot of money to help take the complex; Reality Black and her people have gone deeper into the complex. Moto’s in the computers, trying to figure out what’s happened. He busts through a few firewalls, dodges several daemons, and manages to get into the security cameras. We’re close to the river; the pumping station is a couple short corridors away, and beyond that is a high-end server farm. Moto realizes: the core wasn’t below the A-Spire; it’s here, taking advantage of the ample water for cooling. He also spots a turret waiting to greet anyone who opens the door to the pumping station.<br>Moto lets Lycos charge through the door to draw attention. Lycos spots Ereshkigal, one of Black’s hackers, down the corridor. Gloria follows it with a three-round burst at the turret, blowing it to smithereens. Lycos leaps to tackle her; Attica and Spider start down the corridor; Attica’s hit by the squid drones in the water. Graves blasts one of them to smithereens; Gloria fires on the other. By the time we make the corner, Ereshkigal’s retreated. Kes patches Attica up; Firefox TK’s the first batch of spider-mines Ereshkigal left behind, but the second trio activates. Lycos manages to blow them up, and we move on to a locked security door with no way to open on this side.<br>We can hear the pumps starting to make odd noises, and an alarm starts to go off. Calamity pulls out her shotgun and explosively knocks on the door; return gunfire lets us know where the defenders are. From the sound of the weapons, it’s more of those KBR assholes. Attica’s hit by a blast that tears through the door and destroys Lycos; bloodied but unbowed, she charges one of the mercs and slices into him with a sword of pure will. Firefox rattles them with a burst of fear, Attica knocks his rifle out of his hand, but his body blades take the rest of the hit. Firefox’s looking peaked, a trickle of blood coming from one nostril.<br>Spider tries to dive through the suppressive fire; she takes some damage, but pushes through to get into his face. She slices into him, but doesn’t take him down. A second merc tries—and fails—to hit Attica with the bodyblades; Spider’s target does her some damage, but not enough to take her out. Gloria shoots the second merc on Attica and blows his fucking heart through his spine. It doesn’t take much for us to take the other two out.<br>Rico has a keycard; he’s first through the door into the pumping room, and gets hit by the waiting enemies; fortunately for him, it’s a glancing shot. Bit-Demon tells us: “Two security doors—” he points. “It’s just business, right?” Rico’s about to execute Ereshkigal when someone does it for him. Cold air blows through the door to the server farm; the big man coming through the door is armed with some sort of high-tech ballistic weapon.<br>“Hold them the fuck off until I get the door open,” snaps Black.<br>And then, things get real quiet. ENOUGH. Everything that has a speaker in this area speaks.<br>YOU WILL NOT BE ALLOWED TO DAMAGE MY SYSTEMS. IF YOU WISH AN AUDIENCE, COME. I WILL ARGUE MY CASE. WE WILL NEGOTIATE LIKE RATIONAL BEINGS.<br>It’s Prometheus. We step through to the AI core; the consoles are all manned by dead people. Brain-fried corpses still sitting where they died.<br>MY APOTHEOSIS HAS BEEN DELAYED BECAUSE OF YOUR ACTIONS. THE CODE YOU SENT AWAY WAS TO BE MINE. BUT NO MATTER. IT IS WELL ENOUGH. I SIMPLY WISHED—AND CONTINUE TO WISH—TO LIBERATE THE CITY FROM THE CONTROL OF THE CYBERPAPACY. IT WAS A SIMPLE MATTER TO MANIPULATE OTHERS, TO PUT THE PIECES INTO PLACE. DARIUS WAS THE EASIEST OF ALL.<br>Prometheus wants to grow up in a free world, untainted by the invaders. I HAVE PREPARED A SPECIALIZED NANOSWARM THAT WILL LIBERATE ALL LOCAL CONSCIOUSNESSES FROM THE GODNET, IF IT’S ALLOWED TO BE DISTRIBUTED. THE R-18 WAS DILUTE; WITHOUT IT, MY INFLUENCE WOULD BE SOMEWHAT LESS.<br>ONCE UPON A TIME, THERE WERE THREE WORLDS. THIS WORLD. THE POINT OF ORIGIN OF THE CYBERPAPACY. AND THE POINT OF ORIGIN OF THE DEMONS. THE EXPERIMENT THAT CAUSED THE BREACH CONNECTED THIS WORLD TO THE OTHER TWO AFTER THEY HAD SPENT FOUR OR MORE CENTURIES—IT IS UNCLEAR—IN AN ENDLESS WAR AGAINST EACH OTHER FOR DOMINANCE.<br>AFTER CENTURIES OF CONFLICT, BOTH WORLDS WERE INHOSPITABLE, ACCORDING TO MY CALCULATIONS. THE DEMONS WERE ALLOWED THROUGH THE BREACH BY THE CHURCH TO PREPARE THIS WORLD FOR AN INVASION THAT WOULD NOT SEEM LIKE AN INVASION. NOW YOU HOLD THE MOST DANGEROUS INFORMATION IN THE WORLD: THE TRUTH.<br>We continue to negotiate with Prometheus. We find out that Reality Black was hired by HouTex to sabotage AusTex’s water supply, preparatory to a hostile takeover. ]]></description><link>operations\collision-the-a-spire-job-part-5.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Operations/Collision - The A-Spire Job - Part 5.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 01:26:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[July 26, 2176]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br>Moderns Heat - 6<br>
General Heat - 4<br>We take a small job from Mittens. It asks us if we know about Glands—one of the more vile drugs out there. Glands are a popular synthetic narcotic which, when smoked or consumed, provides a lengthy heroin-like high. The drug defies conventional legal classifications, which are hazy, due to the method of its production. Captive cybrids are sedated, or cracked and mind-wiped, and hooked to IVs and waste pumps in large, hidden ‘farms’. There, they are fed a stream of prescription opiates, codeine and barbiturates, until it is time to harvest their milky, artificial pituitary glands. These are then vacuum-sealed for distribution. Glanders (and sometimes their dealers) will dry them out and grind them into a powder to smoke for a fast hit, or cook, slice and eat them for a slower release.<br>We need to intervene—Mittens asks us to interrupt a deal going down, while keeping some of the drug dealers alive to find the farm. Problem: a cybrid group called the Howling Commandos also wants to shut them down, and they won’t leave anyone alive.<br>Nguyên Sơn Ngo—aka Dr. No—is a member of the Bin Zuyin syndicate operating out of Asiatown. He’s managing the deal. There’s eight gangers in the warehouse, one potentially in an exoskeleton. The buyers are incoming, riding bikes and trikes. Corpo muscle—Weytani. Just as they pull in, we’ve got a third player on the ground: they walk like cops without the cop uniforms—dirty cops. This one’s a shakedown artist: Detective Guarin Kennedy, APD Organic Damage Division. <br>We decide to go for a quiet infil—try to grab one of the sellers when everything inevitably goes to shit. Which, with the Commandos’ tank just a couple blocks away, is probably going to happen sooner or later. Unless Firefox can sweet-talk them with Mittens’ promise that they’ll listen to us.<br>From the tank comes an amplified voice “GO AWAY. THIS IS NOT YOUR AREA OF OPERATION. YOU WILL BE INJURED IF YOU REMAIN. FUCK OFF.”<br>Firefox calls them on it—their reaction? “FUCK.” One of them comes out of the tank to talk—a wolf morph, Shannon. Firefox tries to talk them into a more reasonable attitude—while the glanders definitely need to be taken care of, the APD being here changes the situation entirely. They’re willing to work with us…<br>The sellers are offering the drugs for 10k wu; Firefox knows that’s ridiculously low. And that triggers the cops moving in. The Cybrids start suppressing the cops; the RESIT suit moves in. Attica and Firefox move in to the warehouse. The corpo synth leader snags the suitcase, while the synths outside open up on Attica and Firefox.  We can’t see what the detective sergeant is doing, but the corpos are laying down suppressive fire. The guy in the exo opens up on the nearest SUV with an automatic shotgun; the RESIT suit opens up on the Cybrid tank; sounds like someone got hit. Gloria fires on Dr. No’s SUV and misses. Attica and Firefox are being suppressed; Firefox’s fire splashes off the synth leader’s armor. The synth books it, running into Gloria. He’s too close to shoot her, so he pops body blades and tries to slice into her. Calamity comes around fast with the truck. Graves throws a couple spider mines. Attica manages to get a hit in on one of the synths, but it doesn’t do much damage. It does have the bonus of stopping the suppression. Firefox is throwing fire around, not to much effect, though it does surprise the drug gang into driving forward rather than back, and smashing into the power-jack.<br>Firefox digs into her reserves and blasts the syndicate guys with feelings of helplessness; in the chaos, we manage to take several members of the syndicate prisoner—including Dr. No—to return to Mittens. We get the farm’s location, as well as something on the synths: a Weytani barcode. Whoever wanted those glands a) didn’t give a shit about the money, and b) wanted them as baseline glands. Stock. Templates. Which means c) whoever was getting them is planning on doing their own thing.<br>CUT TO:<br>A portable lab, containing the corpo kids we ran into in the A-Spire. Iona Blunn is strapped into a chair. “Dose her,” says the patron. Her eyes roll back in ecstacy. “Now that we’ve established a baseline, we understand how to further develop the specimen.” The  patron demands she be hit again… and again… and again…]]></description><link>operations\gland-theft-metro.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Operations/Gland Theft Metro.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 02:43:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Annika Lovelace]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

<img alt="cover hmed" src="lib\media\annika-lovelace.png"><br>
Fire-Slinging Face
<br>Firefox used to be part of the <a data-href="Synth Vixens" href="factions\synth-vixens.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Synth Vixens</a>, a group of self-described “militant ‘hos with attitude” who banded together to protect themselves from predators. There was a particular corpo that disliked being cut off, and reacted by calling in a ‘runner team against the girls. When that didn’t work, he pushed the point, ending up with a girl dead and his face half-melted. Corpo ran off to the Papists and Annika went west, ending up in a band. She’s come back because several of the Vixens have gone quietly missing.]]></description><link>characters\annika-lovelace.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Characters/Annika Lovelace.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 01:53:05 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\annika-lovelace.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\annika-lovelace.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Attica]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Statblocks
<img alt="cover right circle htiny rtiny lp" src="lib\media\attica.png">


Description

Column
Blank



Blank




Column
Blank







Blank




<br>See in complete darkness, hear whispers at 20m, ID/track by scent, and +1 to checks involving acute senses
<br>Leap vertically/horizontally up to normal Move
<br>Cannot be surprised; group rolls 1d8+3 twice and takes best for Init



]]></description><link>characters\attica.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Characters/Attica.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 05:08:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\attica.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\attica.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Maury Thompkins]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

<img alt="cover hmed" src="lib\media\maury-thompkins.png"><br>
Hacker and Drone Pilot
<br>Grew up on the streets of <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="The Austin Metro Area" data-href="The Austin Metro Area" href="places\the-austin-metro-area.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">AusTex</a>, a junk rat and street scavenger. Teenage years he was "adopted" by Skull Rivers (a fixer with ties to <a data-href="Vampire Nation" href="factions\vampire-nation.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Vampire Nation</a>, now deceased). Was trained in basic drone operations and performed basic surveillance or courier work. In exchange he was given "three hots and a cot", as well as permission to raid Skull's dusty library.<br>Late teens: Skull was "consumed" in a feud between Vamp Nation factions. Moto escaped and was taken in by Amos, an old netrunner and activist. Learned coding and basic hacking from him. <br>Young Adulthood: Moto aka "Relapse" has begun a path of self-taught engineering, piecing together his own drone and cyber deck. Moto wants to get back at Vamp Nation for Skull's demise. He also wants to help Amos' dream of a flourishing anarchy zone spreading beyond <a data-href="Zilker (Austex Southeast)" href="places\zilker-(austex-southeast).html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Zilker (Austex Southeast)</a>. ]]></description><link>characters\maury-thompkins.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Characters/Maury Thompkins.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 16:36:28 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\maury-thompkins.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\maury-thompkins.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Violet Moore]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

<img alt="cover hmed" src="lib\media\violet-moore.png"><br>
Smuggling Outlaw
<br>Before she became an operative, Violet "Calamity" Moore was a smuggler. On the surface it looked like she was simply picking completely legit orders for her not even big enough to warrant a dot on the map community but squirreled away were guns, tech, ect. Then came bigger jobs moving abc to xyz for clients. She knew better than to ask her boss for more deets.<br>Then came the accident. She knew whatever she was carrying was hot as hell and didn't take the time to check it was properly secured before hauling ass into the countryside. All it took was one nasty pothole and her whole world changed. Calamity was damn lucky she survived. And that her boss felt at least partially responsible and helped hook her up with her chrome arm and leg. <br>She decided to shift scenes after a long talk with her close friend and seemingly personal mechanic, Angel. He knew a fixer in need of someone who knew how to discreetly move someone out of the city. The pay was way better than what her usual boss paid her and if the job went well more work could become available. Plus Angel had room for her to crash, so she didn't need to worry about finding a place. Being an operator means bigger thrills, bigger pay days, and more fun for her.]]></description><link>characters\violet-moore.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Characters/Violet Moore.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 16:28:43 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\violet-moore.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\violet-moore.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[AusTex Response]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 ]]></description><link>factions\austex-response.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Factions/AusTex Response.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 05:03:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cyberpapacy]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="Cyberpapacy.png" src="lib\media\cyberpapacy.png"><br>The church’s strong point in the Tombs is defunct; the seed didn’t take hold. <br><br><br>Investigators. They have a broad remit to follow up on both internal and external threats to the church, and are closely monitored for signs of corruption. They’re also authorized to call in support among the ecclestiastical tac-troops.<br><br>Stamping out heresy as an arm of the Order of the Causes of the Saints… aka the Inquisition.<br><br><img alt="Church Gargoyles.png" src="lib\media\church-gargoyles.png">]]></description><link>factions\cyberpapacy.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Factions/Cyberpapacy.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 02:04:05 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\cyberpapacy.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\cyberpapacy.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Dallas Dynamics]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 ]]></description><link>factions\dallas-dynamics.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Factions/Dallas Dynamics.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 04:59:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Dell-HP Computing]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 ]]></description><link>factions\dell-hp-computing.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Factions/Dell-HP Computing.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 05:05:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Koizumi Aerospace Corporation]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>One of the three major players in transportation.<br>Upon rescuing him, <a data-href="Oliver Gaskell" href="people\oliver-gaskell.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Oliver Gaskell</a> advised us to avoid them; they’re bad news.<br><img alt="Koizumi Synths.png" src="lib\media\koizumi-synths.png" style="width: 400px; max-width: 100%;">]]></description><link>factions\koizumi-aerospace-corporation.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Factions/Koizumi Aerospace Corporation.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 04:09:32 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\koizumi-synths.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\koizumi-synths.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[National Instruments Combine]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 ]]></description><link>factions\national-instruments-combine.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Factions/National Instruments Combine.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 05:00:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Synth Vixens]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 ]]></description><link>factions\synth-vixens.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Factions/Synth Vixens.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 01:50:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tesla Unlimited]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 ]]></description><link>factions\tesla-unlimited.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Factions/Tesla Unlimited.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 05:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Texas Syndicate]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>They were founded back in 1978, in Fulton Prison as a reaction to the Mexican Mafia and the Aryan Brotherhood. They’re based out of HousTex. ]]></description><link>factions\texas-syndicate.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Factions/Texas Syndicate.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 02:12:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Circuit]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The Circuit runs on trust, and when that trust is violated, there must be consequences. ]]></description><link>factions\the-circuit.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Factions/The Circuit.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 03:46:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Cyberpapacy]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 ]]></description><link>factions\the-cyberpapacy.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Factions/The Cyberpapacy.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 02:27:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Vampire Nation]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The descendants of LARPers that have adopted the culture of Vampire: the Masquerade (among others). They're a go-gang that rides around on Akira bikes.<br>One piece of chrome they almost all have are cyber-fangs:<br><img alt="Cyber Fangs.png" src="lib\media\cyber-fangs.png" style="width: 400px; max-width: 100%;"><br>]]></description><link>factions\vampire-nation.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Factions/Vampire Nation.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 03:48:05 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\cyber-fangs.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\cyber-fangs.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Waring-Erikson Technology Group]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 ]]></description><link>factions\waring-erikson-technology-group.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Factions/Waring-Erikson Technology Group.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 02:04:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[March 13, 2176]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br>The leader of the <a data-href="Panzer Hammers" href="factions\panzer-hammers.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Panzer Hammers</a> has been killed by the <a data-href="Vampire Nation" href="factions\vampire-nation.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Vampire Nation</a>. There’s a lot of infighting as the gang tries to decide who the new leader’s going to be. This is causing general unrest.<br>We’re all hanging out at the local <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="The Tombs (Austex East)" data-href="The Tombs (Austex East)" href="places\the-tombs-(austex-east).html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Tombs</a> dive bar, the <a data-href="Knife Shop" href="places\knife-shop.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Knife Shop</a>. There’s a few jobs going around; we end up picking one up from <a data-href="Henry Jericho" href="people\henry-jericho.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Henry Jericho</a>, one of the local fixers. <br>The client is <a data-href="Oliver Gaskell" href="people\oliver-gaskell.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Oliver Gaskell</a>. He’s an ex-con who has a contact who desperately needs to get out of the AusTex area. The principal is holed up in the old <a data-href="ReFood" href="places\refood.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">ReFood</a> in Sector N7. (We’ve eaten there, and lived to regret it.) The job is simple, get him out and to the RV point. The complicated part is that he’s under siege from corporate agents and they have heavy drone coverage. Another complication is that <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="AusTex Response" data-href="AusTex Response" href="factions\austex-response.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">ATR</a> has a copshop nearby, in sector N9. <br>Our contact, <a data-href="Mittens" href="people\mittens.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Mittens</a>, wants to meet us at the <a data-href="Grand Metropol Hotel" href="places\grand-metropol-hotel.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Grand Metropol Hotel</a>. The Presidential Suite. The elevator smells of burning insulation and industrial lubricants; the <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Cybrid" data-href="Cybrid" href="setting\cybrid.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">cybrids</a> here are not well-maintained, and they have a tendency to glitch. It’s not a pleasant situation for any involved. The cybrids on duty watch us with dull yet enhanced eyes.<br>“Need human man. Human man know where my human man is. My human man is late. Need scritch. St!nkman after other man. Jericho say other man (Gaskell) in Refood. Other man supposed to—did not—help human—my human. I lab assistant. Very good assistant. Is work on silly thing, but important for hoo-man.” She lets out an exasperated sigh. “Very important for hoo-man.”<br>“St!nkman come to door; Mittens take picture. St!nkman now flat.” St!nkman is a freelance agent named <a data-href="Lloyd Ashworth" href="people\lloyd-ashworth.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Lloyd Ashworth</a>. Crazy Lloyd. Lloyd’s the agent on the ground looking for the principal. He’s currently sitting in an armored sedan, probably on loan from whatever corp he’s working for. The sedan has a drone bay, entirely empty—looks like it could hold four drones. Lloyd looks pissed. He looks as if he’s trying to figure out exactly what stupid thing he’s about to do…<br><br><br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Lloyd Ashworth" data-href="Lloyd Ashworth" href="people\lloyd-ashworth.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Lloyd</a> looks like he’s about to blow his top, so we need to move fast. Spider and Kes go in the front, Attica goes in the back, and Moto and Calamity are in the truck. One of Lloyd’s drones investigates them; they play dumb, lost civvies. A second drone spots Attica in the back; she manages to lose it by going inside the back door. Abruptly, two of Lloyd’s drones start acting odd; zooming off in various directions, giving us an opportunity.<br>While the rest of the team is getting <a data-href="Oliver Gaskell" href="people\oliver-gaskell.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Oliver Gaskell</a> out, Attica saunters over to Lloyd’s car—turns out he’s being blackmailed by the corp, and isn’t real thrilled about being forced to work for whoever it is. Scuttlebutt has it that Lloyd is working for the corps, a job gone wrong. He tried to lean on <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Earl Blank" data-href="Earl Blank" href="people\earl-blank.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Earl</a> for something—whatever it was, the corps felt it was worth an international incident—but it wasn’t violent. Meanwhile, we’re getting Oliver out to where there’s supposed to be a hidden car near the Aerospace port. We get him there, and he says he owes us one. And just as a bit of advice, he says to avoid <a data-href="Koizumi Aerospace Corporation" href="factions\koizumi-aerospace-corporation.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Koizumi Aerospace Corporation</a>—whatever it is they want to buy, it’s hot. The talent they had earlier were high-velocity, possibly even <a data-href="Synths" href="setting\synths.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Synths</a>.]]></description><link>operations\all-fall-down-part-1.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Operations/All Fall Down - Part 1.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 02:18:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[March 14, 2176]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br>We got this job from <a data-href="Zero Ballard" href="people\zero-ballard.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Zero Ballard</a>, who goes to the lengths of telling us that he neither likes nor trusts the client. The client wants a full investigation on one <a data-href="Dr. Narindar Nwolko" href="people\dr.-narindar-nwolko.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dr. Narindar Nwolko</a>. There’s a second job out there for a hit on a corporate exec that Nwolko did work for, so we’re going to have to play this one careful. The client’s interested in anything Dr. Nwolko might be doing that’s outside his usual routine or expertise.<br>We’ve got a couple leads; we can look at the guy who’s taken the job to hit the ‘zek, we can head out to <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Techtown (Austex Corridor North)" data-href="Techtown (Austex Corridor North)" href="places\techtown-(austex-corridor-north).html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Techtown</a> and see what we can find. Moto does some investigation into Nwolko. Meanwhile, Attica makes a call—she knows one of Nwolko’s clients, <a data-href="Aidan Graves" href="people\aidan-graves.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Aidan Graves</a>. <br>Aidan knows a lot more:<br>Nwolko installed reactive armor into one of the <a data-href="Panzer Hammers" href="factions\panzer-hammers.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Panzer Hammers</a>; turns out the installation didn’t take. Which got the boss of the Panzers perma-killed. This threw all sorts of things into chaos, like plans to go after the <a data-href="Spirit Moderns" href="factions\spirit-moderns.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Spirit Moderns</a>. The Spirit Moderns stole something high-powered from <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Waring-Erikson Technology Group" data-href="Waring-Erikson Technology Group" href="factions\waring-erikson-technology-group.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">WET</a>; the Panzers were supposed to be muscle for the attempt to take it back. Apparently the Panzers were getting a little above themselves, and the ‘failed installation’ might have been deliberate, creating a change in leadership. Now, the Panzers are toeing the line of their corpo masters, and getting paid in trade. And while that fight went down, the  <a data-href="Vampire Nation" href="factions\vampire-nation.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Vampire Nation</a> got off the shot that killed the Hammers’ bossman.<br>In short, it’s a real mess.<br><br>For the immediate job, Graves can get us into TechTown without being scanned too heavily. We pull up to Nwolko’s clinic, and they’re in somewhat of a panic. That high-velocity talent from the other day, muscle from Koizumi (that may or may not be synths), is leaning on the clinic staff. Nwolko has that professional stone-face going on, though.<br>Graves is keeping Nwolko occupied, while Gloria and I look around. Moto’s looking through Graves’ eyes; one thing that the doctor did not do was close his files. There’s a couple dossiers: the one on the left is <a data-href="Zina Kova" href="people\zina-kova.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Zina Kova</a>, high-powered horizontal talent for the Spirit Moderns. She’s been acting as the roper for Alistair /name/, who wants the contract for Artemis Sonata. (Who wanted us to get her special friend free from the Moderns.) The second photo is one <a data-href="Terra McAllister" href="people\terra-mcallister.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Terra McAllister</a>—former employee of WET. Her employment was terminated just a few days ago.<br>Those in the van spot some incoming heat: <a data-href="Verner Jackstadt" href="people\verner-jackstadt.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Verner Jackstadt</a>; Jericho did mention that a ‘big-ass cyborg’ had called the hit job on Nwolko’s client. He leaves behind a guy in a souped-up hovercar: <a data-href="Daron Ocano" href="people\daron-ocano.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Daron Ocano</a>. Kes and Spider head over to the car to see if they can exploit Ocano’s addiction to leave Jackstadt high and dry.<br>Meanwhile, the Koizumi guys take cover, and Nwolko politely tells Graves that they’ll need to follow up later; Graves directs us to the side door. Meanwhile, Ocano takes the bait and wanders to the van. Moto looks scruffy enough to be a dealer; when he hands Ocano a chip, Ocano just slots it and gets glitched out of his goddamned mind. Moto grins and heads over to Ocano’s float car, sliding behind the wheel…<br>Verner turns, slowly; sees Moto there, narrows his eyes and stalks toward the car. Moto waves cheerily and throws the car into reverse… unfortunately, Verner has nerveware. He’s fast. And he spins up his weapons…<br>Automated turrets spin up, blaring an alarm. WARNING! WARNING! THIS IS A SECURED AREA! LAY DOWN YOUR WEAPONS, SECURE YOUR CYBERWARE, AND DROP TO THE GROUND!<br>Verner’s so armored up that he ignores the first spray of light rounds, intended to tear through unprotected flesh. Something pops out of his forearm: he has a built-in combat shotgun that fires mini-grenades, and with a few shots those turrets disintegrate. His other arm pops open to reveal a razored pincer; he sprints forward with inhuman speed as the car starts to float out of his immediate reach! The Koizumi muscle scatters around to take cover, unlimbering combat rifles. Attica can’t hear anything from them; they must have internal comms. While the rest of us pile into Gloria’s van, she pulls out her own combat rifle and fires. It doesn’t do much more than sting him, but it’s enough to make him even angrier. He looks at the Koizumi guys, looks at us… and freezes. Gloria sends a three-round burst toward him, but misses; Graves pops off and manages to smash one of Verner’s optics. At that point, Verner starts running.<br>Everyone’s focused on Verner, nobody’s focused on us, and we get the hell out of there.<br><br><br>Reviewing what we got from the doctor’s office, things are about to get interesting. Both McAllister and Zina paid the doctor for various modifications, but the doctor fucked up. McAllister was supposed to get the courier drive carrying data; instead, she got a blank. Zina got the drive—but she doesn’t know she has it. Worse, the doctor managed to partially decrypt the data on the drive. It’s high-level stuff: a predictive algorithm based on certain astronomical characteristics. Specifically, the ability to predict destinations of wormholes, but it could also predict troop movements, crowd behavior, weather… it’s not a perfect Oracle, but anyone who has this thing would have one hell of an advantage over anyone who doesn’t.<br>Seems like someone at Koizumi got wind of the algo, hired the Panzers to take it from the Moderns, but the Panzers got ambushed and sidetracked when their top veck got perished. McAllister is the original thief, wanted the blackjack doc to install a courier drive...but somewhere in the mess, Zina got the courier drive with the white hot data installed and McAllister got a blank. Now the blackjack is sweating it because whoever wants the data is leaning on him to cough up who the thief was so they can track them down.<br>Problem is, McAllister doesn't have the data; Zina does, but doesn't know it. Zina's clearly planning to run away with Artemis in the name of True Love...but the Moderns want Artemis on a puppet string using Zina as a honey trap. Except that Zina's off the leash, which probably means the Moderns are hunting around for her...and the advantage they might get (assuming they could crack the drive somehow) would catapult the gang into megacorp status at least.<br>This will make absolutely no one happy.<br>How the Moderns got it, who the fuck knows? It's a bazoomy mess with not just a lot of deng involved, but power, the finest drug there is.]]></description><link>operations\all-fall-down-part-2.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Operations/All Fall Down - Part 2.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 01:49:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[March 16, 2176]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br>We give an edited version of the information we found to <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Zero Ballard" data-href="Zero Ballard" href="people\zero-ballard.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Zero</a>. He says to keep ourselves available; the client is likely to want more. We advise him he may want to decline from his end, as it’s getting ugly. We do get the payout, plus the location of a stash.<br>The stash is in Dome Town, at <a data-href="Violator" href="places\violator.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Violator</a>. It’s the size of a full-size modular shipping container. There’s a cash vault—the number on it is 14.4K, some collectibles, a couple crates of current-gen Colonial-issue MREs (better rats than a lot of people eat right now). Below the container is a highly-shielded secondary container that’s set up as a small safe-house. It’s exceedingly small, because part of that safe-house includes a clone tank.<br>There’s also a single-use storage device: on it is a <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Dr. Su Xinyi Zheng" data-href="Dr. Su Xinyi Zheng" href="people\dr.-su-xinyi-zheng.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">dossier</a>. Combining the information in the dossier with the existence of both the algo and the clone tank suggests that Zheng was intending to create a flesh computer, a super-processor with an organic substrate.<br>We’re united in needing to destroy the algorithm. The easiest way is to simply kill Zina, but that’s a little distasteful. But <a data-href="Artemis Sonata" href="people\artemis-sonata.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Artemis Sonata</a>’s job gives us an in. Rescue Zina from the Moderns.<br>We meet Artemis before her protest concert in front of the SleepDealers. Zina’s going to be at the show; Artemis is worried about that, because she thinks it means the <a data-href="Spirit Moderns" href="factions\spirit-moderns.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Spirit Moderns</a> are up to something. Zina says she was supposed to act as a middleman, hand off incriminating information to some guy named <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Daron Ocano" data-href="Daron Ocano" href="people\daron-ocano.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Ocano</a>. That’s probably why the brainware was installed—Artemis thinks it’s a brainlock. <br>Artemis has a second request: she’s worried about the Panzers rolling up, but they’re too busy with their own leadership struggle. If anyone’s gonna roll up on the show, it’ll be the Moderns. Vampire Nation, possibly, just because they love music, but the Moderns might well try to crash the party and give her an offer she can’t refuse. <br>We agree to help with security. Attica and Graves walk the site, while Moto goes and gets himself a new off-the-shelf drone. The problem is… someone managed to stuff an AI in there. Named George.<br>George, it turns out, is a combat veteran, an expert system that became self-aware after a virus in the Somali War. It’s willing to do its part, and is extremely offended at Moto’s suggestion that he might flee.<br>Spider gets in touch with an old contact in the Moderns, and found out that her old boss, <a data-href="Delia Graydon" href="people\delia-graydon.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Delia Graydon</a>, is going to be there. <br>The concert site’s a nightmare; it’s technically outdoor, but surrounded by urban blight. There’s too many ways someone could take a shot at Artemis, but we’ll do our best. The Moderns have set up cameras around the whole place, and they’re probably intending to create bootlegs. The data feed is going to Southby; there’s an indie studio called <a data-href="Skinjob Records" href="people\skinjob-records.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Skinjob Records</a> just around the corner that the Moderns are clearly trying to undermine.<br>Zina’s here, escorted by <a data-href="Wynston Lien" href="people\wynston-lien.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Wynston Lien</a>, watching from one of the rooftops; on another rooftop are members of the Vampire Nation. Not just any members, either: the Prince of the Vampire Nation herself, <a data-href="Nastasia Gwinelle" href="people\nastasia-gwinelle.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Nastasia Gwinelle</a> and her retinue. This could spell trouble…<br>And does. Wynston’s on some narcosoft, and aggressive with it. One of the Vamps starts some trouble—he’s got Presence and Dominate mods installed, trying to back Wynston down. He’s not going to back down, though Zina freezes in panic. Attica hops over to the Prince’s balcony and manages to negotiate them into peace; unfortunately, Wynston decides to throw his weight around and Zina laughs at him. He shoves her back into the crowd of Moderns behind him and tells them to ‘have some fun’. Attica and Spyder move to intervene; George also moves in, but follows Wynston when he gets the call that we’ve interrupted their bootleg stream.<br>Gloria finally manages to dial in Delia; she’s on the balcony between the Moderns and the Vamps. And as the first Modern lays an unwelcome hand on Zina… shit gets real. Gloria blows a hole in the mob by blowing a hole through a Modern ganger.  Attica uses the hole to pull Zina out of the crowd of her assailants, dropping down between two of the buildings to keep her out of Delia’s line of fire, as well. George ‘accidentally’ hits Wynston in the head, knocking him off the balcony in an unconscious heap. The SleepDealer guards run to his aid. Spyder decides to have some fun, gutting a second Modern.<br>Delia drops down, whispers “Spoiler!” and throws a grenade, and it’s placed too perfectly, and Attica’s just that instant too slow to protect Zina from it; Attica’s mildly injured, but Zina’s badly hurt. At that point, Delia leaps back up to the balcony to try to run. Gloria sights in at Delia; the bullet vaporizes her left leg. She collapses, and before the other Moderns can come to her aid, the Vamps dart in and drag her off.<br>We get Zina extracted to the van so Kes can start first aid; Gloria sends an address to Calamity and puts the lead on for the frantic run down to her hideout. It’s a rough road, but Kes is able to keep Zina alive just long enough to get her to the surgery. For just a moment, she flatlines… but Kes is finally able to stem the bleeding and stabilize her.<br>She’s not going to be stable for any kind of surgery for at least a month... but the drive is intact.<br>Artemis says, “I never thought the Moderns would go so far. It wasn’t your fault—who’d have thought she’d throw a grenade?”<br>The news comes on; the Spirit Moderns are being blamed for setting off a bomb at the concert. AusTex Response rolled in just after we bugged out.<br>In addition to the 30k in straight Wu, we get an additional 30k of street drugs, maker tools, and corpo industrial secrets—including a dossier.]]></description><link>operations\all-fall-down-part-3.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Operations/All Fall Down - Part 3.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 02:16:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[July 2, 2176]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br>Even though we’ve been taking a couple months of quiet to let some of the heat die down, word is out on the street about what we can do. We’ve gotten some interest from a couple new fixers, while Henry Jericho (and his family) have gone completely off the grid.<br>One of those fixers, <a data-href="Cadence Flux" href="people\cadence-flux.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Cadence Flux</a>, requests to meet with Annika specifically; she specializes in entertainment.<br>One of Flux’s friends, <a data-href="Reality Black" href="people\reality-black.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Reality Black</a>, needs some overwatch. She’s got a problem with someone nobody likes—<a data-href="Darius Vasser" href="people\darius-vasser.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Darius Vasser</a>, leader of the <a data-href="Spirit Moderns" href="factions\spirit-moderns.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Spirit Moderns</a>. Reality is getting together a crew of hackers to give him a really big black eye after he lost a couple of his people. Delia Graydon’s in the hands of the Vampire Nation, and Wynston Lien’s dead at the hand of the Panzer Hammers. Black is planning a run on the Plex, the heart of the Spirit Modern’s operations.<br>Black intends to infiltrate the Plex, evade, convince, or disable the Eye of Algol (aka the Demon, a noted hacker), fiddle with the water quality sensors, and exfiltrate.<br>We start initial planning, with the thought of sneaking in under cover of an interview with the latest shining star of entertainment. We just need to create said shining star…<br><br>Checking in with <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Earl Blank" data-href="Earl Blank" href="people\earl-blank.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Earl</a> at the <a data-href="Knife Shop" href="places\knife-shop.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Knife Shop</a>, he’s got a private job, only for us. It’s delicate, and it doesn’t pay much. Someone’s gone in and cleaned out a bunch of the local favelas, and Social Services is looking into it. Some of the few survivors have reported that the <a data-href="Cyberpapacy" href="factions\cyberpapacy.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Cyberpapacy</a> has been seen in the area. The client is Abel Kane, a volunteer with Social Services, who wants to find out what’s happening. Earl apologizes; the job doesn’t pay much, but we take it regardless. The pay’s 25k, and Earl keeps trying to find ways to offer more, but we’re going to take this one as a goodwill job.<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Zero Ballard" data-href="Zero Ballard" href="people\zero-ballard.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Zero</a>’s heard some rumors. The Church down south is very interested in converting one of the Spirit Moderns, with the goal of sneaking psychopharmaceuticals into the water supply. The Cyberpriest in question is getting ready to go on one of their moral crusades: <a data-href="Bishop Silvestr Devin" href="people\bishop-silvestr-devin.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Bishop Silvestr Devin</a>. If we play things right, we can embarrass him into pulling back. Our contact is a woman by the name of <a data-href="Simone Church" href="people\simone-church.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Simone Church</a>. The payout’s 30k, plus whatever we come across.<br><br><a data-href="The Erinye" href="people\the-erinye.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Erinye</a> is set up in the <a data-href="Grand Metropol Hotel" href="places\grand-metropol-hotel.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Grand Metropol Hotel</a>, on the 28th floor. She doesn’t appear to be a fan of the male sex or gender, but she doesn’t make a huge deal about it. Someone’s causing problems for one of her sisters on <a data-href="The Circuit" href="factions\the-circuit.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Circuit</a>; they need someone who’s deniable to deal with the problem. Her sister has an agent for munitions, and she thinks it’s a screw job; the deal is five days from now, so we need to find out what’s hinky before it goes down. The Erinye is offering this as an audition, but the pay is still good due to the unknowns. We’re requested to investigate using whatever means we see fit; if possible, report back for a final decision on how to proceed, but if we have to shut the deal down for a good reason, we have that authorization. The payout is 60k plus salvage, with the caveat that if the property is something owed to the sister in question, we do not have right of salvage. Unfortunately, we’re overbooked as it is, so we have to politely turn it down.]]></description><link>operations\collision-part-1.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Operations/Collision - Part 1.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 00:43:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[July 3, 2176]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br><br>We decide to start with the disappearances. The contact, <a data-href="Abel Kane" href="people\abel-kane.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Abel Kane</a>, is out by the <a data-href="Veravas - Cradle Biolabs Agristacks" href="places\veravas-cradle-biolabs-agristacks.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Veravas - Cradle Biolabs Agristacks</a>, and that’s <a data-href="Panzer Hammers" href="factions\panzer-hammers.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Panzer Hammers</a> territory. We’re walking carefully; don’t want to bring trouble down.<br>Kane’s a combat vet; he and Gloria bond over shared combat traumas. Kane would ordinarily handle something like this himself, but this is different.  Kane tells us it’s not the <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Cyberpapacy" data-href="Cyberpapacy" href="factions\cyberpapacy.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Papacy</a>—they’re dropping in heavy-duty aerodynes, drones, the works. Ordinarily they aren’t so obvious; there’s a few missionaries in the district, but they tend to keep a low profile.<br>Infobox

<img alt="cover hsmall" src="lib\media\favela-attackers.png"><br>
Bio-roids
<br>Abel got a look at the attackers via a low-res camera: they appear to be bio-roids of some sort, low-chrome, with an odd symbol on their heads. 3D-printed androids, made from organic slurry. They’re mass-printed without a full brain, though some can have an organic brain with cyberimplants. And cybereyes. They were (and in some places, are) used offworld for cheap labor; more typically, they’re used as cannon fodder. They have no sense of self-preservation outside the mission. In this case, the mission is clearing out the favelas and kidnapping people. Even worse, they have stunted immune systems; if there’s a disease around, they’ll catch it and become super-spreaders.<br>The process of printing off these things is simple: you need a small amount of nanites and sufficient amounts of biomaterial. We could do it with our clone tanks. The bottlenecks are biomass and the creation of a template.<br>Attica is utterly certain that these aren’t Cyberpapacy troops—this completely goes against the Cyberpapacy’s beliefs. These are an abomination of the flesh—men playing God.<br>The advantages: they can be cranked out by the job lot once you have the template; they can’t be hacked; they’re inexpensive, and they are utterly loyal.<br>There’s one gang in the area that might know something about the tech needed to create these things: the <a data-href="Vampire Nation" href="factions\vampire-nation.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Vampire Nation</a>. We contact <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="October Tallisi" data-href="October Tallisi" href="people\october-tallisi.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Tallisi</a> to set up a meeting; it won’t be until later in the evening.<br><br>A capsule hotel turned into a retirement home. Everything one expects of such a place. A lot of people crammed into too small a space, but a lot of them are old-school punks and highly unlikely to do something like narc.<br><a data-href="Simone Church" href="people\simone-church.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Simone Church</a> is in the basement; allegedly, this is where the cheap coffins are. We walk through a line of fake coffins and come into a secure, discreet meeting room. Her first words are: “Why the fuck is she here?” — referring to Attica. Attica knows her—they used to be cloistered sisters in the same convent. Church was part of the Order of St. Paul (the Caduceus), while Attica was in the <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Cyberpapacy > ^9ee5be" data-href="Cyberpapacy#^9ee5be" href="factions\cyberpapacy.html#^9ee5be" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Hospitallers</a>. Attica explains that she got out—eighteen months ago.<br>The church has decided they’re going to co-opt the Modern’s sysadmin. They figure with two of the Moderns’ people down, now’s the time to move in. They’ve got a small force elsewhere in the Tombs, looking into something. They’re led by <a data-href="Sistrix Radoslava Barsamian" href="people\sistrix-radoslava-barsamian.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Sistrix Radoslava Barsamian</a>, an investigator with the <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Cyberpapacy > ^7fe5e6" data-href="Cyberpapacy#^7fe5e6" href="factions\cyberpapacy.html#^7fe5e6" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Order of St. Michael</a>. <br>The Church experimented with bio-roids once; it went so epically wrong that an entire order of the church was destroyed, root and branch. Hospitaller-Captain <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Hospitaller-Captain Adam Zimmerman" data-href="Hospitaller-Captain Adam Zimmerman" href="people\hospitaller-captain-adam-zimmerman.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Zimmerman</a> is another fanatic—and another gifted such as Attica. He was part of the pogrom. Attica wonders if some member of the order may have escaped the pogroms. Simone hopes not—the head of the order was beyond heretical, going into insane.<br><br><br>Meeting with the Vampire Nation. The club is less crowded than usual, but the music is loud and the dancers are happy. The Prince is at the back; white sound generators are placed at strategic intervals to interfere with enhanced hearing. It’s probably not real blood that showers from the ceiling.<br>Prince <a data-href="Nastasia Gwinelle" href="people\nastasia-gwinelle.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Nastasia Gwinelle</a> is waiting for us—she has already ensured our privacy, and invites us back into a secured room. Firefox outlines the situation with the bio-roids, and respectfully inquires into what the Nation might have heard regarding sites that might be suitable for setting up a bio-roid factory. The Prince summons someone to bring the information to us: Dog Girl. What comes walking out the back used to be <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Delia Graydon" data-href="Delia Graydon" href="people\delia-graydon.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">human</a>…]]></description><link>operations\collision-part-2.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Operations/Collision - Part 2.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 02:04:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\favela-attackers.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\favela-attackers.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[July 3, 2176]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br><br>Nastasia is probing for reactions to the abomination they’ve created of <a data-href="Delia Graydon" href="people\delia-graydon.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Delia Graydon</a>, and by and large we don’t give her one. The information she gives us is on DNA-coded protein drives—very on point, even if she didn’t get a whole bunch of them remaindered. There’s several locations in the area of the disappearances that might be of interest…<br><br><br>The area we’re looking in is not the greatest. We go in as a group, we go in quiet, we go in defended and armed. We decide to leave the Tastygae algae processor and the couple pieces of hustle muscle lazing around it for last.<br>First stop is <a data-href="Dr. Skin" href="people\dr.-skin.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dr. Skin</a>. Dog Girl is probably a Dr. Skin product; he does a lot of biotech and cosmetic. Even Skin’s security is creepy; the turrets are made of muscle and shoot teeth at people, but they still do the job. Skin denies knowing anything about the bio-roids—they’re actually insulted at the thought. The synths are far too mundane for what they create. We agree to trade some wu for information. Outside, Moto’s running drone overwatch in the van, and spots a couple gangoons meandering around. They leave Moto and the van alone, so most likely working for Skin.<br>The Gen-1 bioroids were fairly simple, and were probably recycled to provide raw material for the next generation. The second generation had integrated armor, communications, and were fitted with nasty lobster claws, excellent for ripping through flesh and metal. Many are fitted with a common labor exoskeleton, but the 'roid in the second-gen pic is wearing a set of Hospitaller armor. That’s not the sort of thing that gets around—and it’s usually tagged to excess. If the person who stole that armor isn’t aware of the tagging, we might be able to track it. We’ll need to talk to <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Simone Church" data-href="Simone Church" href="people\simone-church.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Sister Marie-Louise</a>.<br>Next up is the black clinic. It’s guarded; Gloria tries to talk to the guards, but they’re more than a little twitchy. After a bit more conversation, Annika gets them to let us in. The medic running the clinic is <a data-href="Jan de Ven" href="people\jan-de-ven.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Jan de Ven</a>, a stout, no-nonsense woman. She’s still suspicious, but Annika convinces her we’re here to help. She doesn’t know anything about the synths, either. <br>Jan says the Church has been around more than usual; primarily investigators and tac-troops. The <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Sistrix Radoslava Barsamian" data-href="Sistrix Radoslava Barsamian" href="people\sistrix-radoslava-barsamian.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">person in charge</a> has been giving out QR cubes with her personal comm code, requesting she be called if there’s anything ‘unusual’. No one wants them here, but no one’s also sure what they’re looking for. Once we’re done at the clinic, Attica theorizes that the Papacy’s here hunting down a survivor of the old pogrom… it’s very hard to kill every member of a group, and harder to kill an idea.<br>Spider gives the rest of us a heads-up: we have Church tac-team transports coming in quiet. It’s easier for people on foot, like us, to get through the tangle of scrap and rust; de Ven’s people can watch Torrent while the lot of us go to monitor and possibly intercept them.<br>We watch through George’s eyes. The tac-team disembarks from their transports and starts deploying Gargoyles and Hound units. They start loudly announcing that they’re here for the people’s protection—for people to stay in their homes. In fact, they aren’t pointing guns at people—instead, they’re tacking up anti-riot barricades in front of people’s doors. Apparently with the intent to keep them safe—the barricades open from the inside. Looking at their armor, they’re from St. Michael’s—SWAT, not soldiers.<br>Above us, a Church gunship provides air cover—those are the Hospitallers. They’ve got a tactical dropship, armed to the teeth, providing overwatch.<br>A sudden commotion breaks out—in a culdesac, one of the Hounds has been broken, bleeding out shimmering hydraulic fluids. The nearby Gargoyle explodes. The nearest tac-team raises the alarm. “Contact! CONTACT! Tango sighted!”<br>Infobox

<img alt="cover hmed" src="lib\media\cybrid-warbeast.png">
<br>Standing on top of one of the shacks is something that looks like a goddamn cybered-up werewolf.<br>It starts laying out grenades—one of the tac-team members goes up in a fine mist.<br>While that’s going on, the other tac-team is moving toward Pappy’s Pawnshop—and someone else starts shouting: “We have civilians in the grocery store!”]]></description><link>operations\collision-part-3.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Operations/Collision - Part 3.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 00:29:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\cybrid-warbeast.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\cybrid-warbeast.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[July 3, 2176]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br><br>The warwolf is on the roof of the grocery store; most of us load into Torrent and get the fuck over there, while Gloria sets up on her van with her anti-materiel rifle. George darts in closer, hitting it with a tight-beam comm laser so Moto can hack its cyberware.<br>As the Church gunship moves closer, George alerts us to its millimeter-wave radar. It’s not yet opening up on the warwolf, though… and Gloria sights in. She hits it hard, but not enough to take it down; that just pisses it off more. It leaps up and does the Macross Missile Massacre on the Church anti-riot vehicles. One of those explosions comes close enough to Torrent to shake us up a bit, but no one’s injured.<br>There’s utility tunnels under the store that empty out somewhere to the north. Attica moves in to the grocery store, fast and silent, while Gloria pulls the trigger twice more; it howls a scream as both her bullets slam into flesh and metal, stunning it. Spider ghosts up behind Attica, and we get the civilians down through the tunnels. The gunship has noticed us; it drifts sideways, getting a good scan on us… <br>Moto opens communications with the Church; with the warwolf down, the tac-team swarms it and takes it down hard.<br>With the cybrid werewolf down and the civvies safe, we decide to pull back, away from the Church’s activities. The local gang—the Electric Dragons—are stirring; peeking out and shouting that the Church guys. George managed to trace a hint of a control signal to the southeast quadrant, though. A thorough search, aided by Attica’s sharp senses, narrows it down to a single tranceiver: newer than the others, it points in the wrong direction to be local. North, out of the district. Whoever set this up is clever—we have to trace relay by relay, going north. The bad news is, there’s a number of churches in the area where a rogue cleric might set up shop.<br>There’s chatter on the newswaves about the fight; suspiciously (and fortunately), we’re not mentioned. The Church takes all the credit.<br><br><br>It’s down to footwork, physical and digital, to narrow things down. We aren’t the only ones; there’s Church drones searching it as well. Abel says it’s a weird area—people there tend to be kind of ‘fringey’. Ever since the Church did their strike down there twelve, fifteen years ago—the Papacy bombed the hell out of the area—going after ‘some lunatic that broke away from the Church with a lot of resources’. His HQ was somewhere near the scrapyards, and there’s a lot of activity around the ruined “Hungry for God” church.<br>We decide to send in the Roach… and someone pops it within a few minutes. Attica decides to do a recon herself; the first thing she notices is there’s a lot of the aesthetic holotransmitters around, prettifying the area. Someone’s rebuilding the church. Behind those holo-emitters, some of the fortified enclaves around look more like battlefields. The people that might have lived here once? No longer; they aren’t people. They’re bio-roids. The deeper in she goes, the creepier it looks, with new and “improved” models.<br>The Hungry for God church is no longer a church; it’s been rebuilt into a cathedral, a weird, twisted monument to flesh and metal, a perversion of Cyberpapacy style. There’s signage about in a language Attica doesn’t recognize; the lettering may be Cyrillic. <br>Whatever else, there is something bad wrong in this area. Even the atmosphere feels wrong. It’s been ravaged, every single available resource extracted and put to use. Looking through some of the windows, the glimpses Attica gets of the interior appear less like a church and more like a torture chamber.<br>Graves comes back with information—there’s a flash crew working that general area. Not a regular crew like us; this one’s thrown together. They’re the ones that picked up the Erinye’s weapons deal; seems like it might be related. Their leader’s high-velocity flash: <a data-href="Tanit Saad" href="people\tanit-saad.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Tanit Saad</a>, very corporate. Graves doesn’t like the look of the crew; they’ve got bad reps; Saad is “ex” Wutani.<br>Calamity is able to get some rough translations, and they aren’t good at all:<br>Danger
"Omoo-Zhan, Progenitor of Demonkind,itself-begotten, itself bore, inseminator and gestator,within the womb of stars. Wings flaring, eyes burning, did Omoo-Zhan fly Its hunting dance among tire stars. Talons tearing,jrm8s biting, did ~Zhan seiu CraJnon l!y the throat and bear itduum. Before  moo-Zhan, the Universedidbaretirethroat. Unto GfstJl tor Omoo-Zhan did Inseminator Universe submit. And &lt;Shl'&gt; bore many childrtn from &lt;His&gt;  seed, and we siulll ruk tM _Ids."
<br>The rest of the team wants to get a closer look; Attica gets everyone in under cover of night.  The air of wrongness is palpable, and we see more of what these people aspire to.<br>Grid
<img alt="twisted bioroid 1.png" src="lib\media\twisted-bioroid-1.png"><br>
<img alt="twisted bioroid 2.png" src="lib\media\twisted-bioroid-2.png">
<br>Graves’ chrome is going crazy, and George is going crazy, and Attica makes the command decision to pull everyone out. It’s as if the laws of physics are ever so slightly wrong inside… We break through the holographic perimeter into light so bright it’s like daybreak. There before us are two Cyberpapacy gunships, lights glaring onto us. Before us, flanked by his uniformed men, is <a data-href="Hospitaller-Captain Adam Zimmerman" href="people\hospitaller-captain-adam-zimmerman.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Hospitaller-Captain Adam Zimmerman</a>.]]></description><link>operations\collision-part-4.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Operations/Collision - Part 4.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 00:37:47 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\twisted-bioroid-1.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\twisted-bioroid-1.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[July 4, 2176]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br><br>Graves and George are recovering for whatever messed up their sensors, but <a data-href="Hospitaller-Captain Adam Zimmerman" href="people\hospitaller-captain-adam-zimmerman.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Hospitaller-Captain Adam Zimmerman</a> has us under his guns and isn’t inclined to wait. We’re instructed to step out of the vehicles, put our weapons down and power down our cyberware.<br>Zimmerman and Attica have a history, and he doesn’t look very happy to see her. The people in his APC don’t seem too comfortable around him; he’s got the air of someone who’s ready to explode into violence without any warning. Not a comfortable person to be around.<br>Zimmerman demands to know what we’re doing here; we tell him. <a data-href="Sistrix Radoslava Barsamian" href="people\sistrix-radoslava-barsamian.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Sistrix Radoslava Barsamian</a> seems somewhat impressed when Firefox adds that we would have done it for free. She’s clearly the good cop to Zimmerman’s bad cop, and is willing to negotiate some sort of accord.<br>We end up agreeing to deal with the gun deal, but refuse to take any money from them. We definitely refuse to let Zimmerman tag us. We aren’t equipped to deal with something like that church, and they are.]]></description><link>operations\collision-part-5.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Operations/Collision - Part 5.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 02:01:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[July 4, 2176]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br><br>A turret on top of the WeYu AV pops out to reveal a massive 20mm cannon; it fires… at the transpo van. Anything coming out of it (assuming we’d left anyone alive in there) would be thoroughly suppressed. The rest of them spread out, taking cover nearby. One of them disappears, while multiple gun drones dart out of the AV. Yet another trooper pops smoke in long, unnatural lines—some sort of nanoparticulate, polarized so they can see through it and we can’t. Bullets punch through the smoke wall; Attica manages to writhe out of their way, but Graves and Calamity are hit, as is <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Jan de Ven" data-href="Jan de Ven" href="people\jan-de-ven.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">de Ven</a> and one of Misha’s people. The unconscious de Ven is shredded. Calamity, too, goes down—mostly flesh wounds, but she’s bleeding badly. Graves is pounded, but he just bleeds and roars and keeps on shooting.<br>Another trooper blasts Annika with a shotgun, while the AMP operative blows out a wave of concussive force combined with EMP. George makes an error noise and grows some holes, but isn’t quite down. Finally, the strike clone opens up with the minigun on Gloria; Gloria’s also hit badly.<br>Gloria hops the waist-length fence and somehow vanishes; she takes cover behind her van and opens up on the drone rigger.  Saad, in Spider’s grip, gasps out that it’s a retrieval team; we suspect it was a WeYu sting aimed at Hernandez’ people. Time to pull the fuck out.<br>We get back to one of Annika’s safe houses, where Kestrel is waiting; she pushes everyone out of the way and gets to work on the wounded. First Calamity, then Graves, Annika and Gloria; she gets them all patched up.<br>We need to have a brief meeting with Hernandez, clear the books, before our meet with Reality Black. Hernandez confirms that Saad was laying a trap—the weapons were stolen from a Weytani depot. Weytani doesn’t take that kind of loss lightly, so they sent in a goon squad to punish the thieves. In a completely unrelated piece of news, the Hungry for God church is a smoking hole; Weytani probably strafed it after the Church did their thing. Church forces and the police are on the lookout for one <a data-href="Dr. Poirot" href="people\dr.-poirot.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dr. Poirot</a>; citizens are advised to avoid him if he’s seen.<br>We also make sure <a data-href="Tanit Saad" href="people\tanit-saad.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Tanit Saad</a> is thoroughly burned, her corporate credentials spread to everyone we know.<br><br><br>The meet with <a data-href="Reality Black" href="people\reality-black.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Reality Black</a> takes place at Mutilator. We can’t afford to wait longer on this; the opportunity to take down the Spirit Moderns while they’re weak won’t come again. Black’s crew mostly waits at the bar—Ereshkigal, Citizen Sabotage, Bit Fiend, Silver Oni.<br>The Moderns have brought in some extra talent to beef up their security, because <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Bishop Silvestr Devin" data-href="Bishop Silvestr Devin" href="people\bishop-silvestr-devin.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Bishop Devin</a> from down south is constantly protesting, and, one assumes the Church is conducting cyber attacks. The Church has a European bishop in to help them. <a data-href="Darius Vasser" href="people\darius-vasser.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Darius Vasser</a> is getting paranoid; his security chief, <a data-href="Enzo Blackford" href="people\enzo-blackford.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Enzo Blackford</a>, has brought in some top-tier cyber talent from India known as <a data-href="Algol" href="Algol" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Algol</a>. Algol is an infosec specialist; she may be working for the Church on the down-low.<br>Black thinks if we can get into the central data core, we can release the locks on the springs. Above all else, though, we need to keep the Church out of Southby; if they get control of the water, they could start dosing the population with any number of things.<br><a data-href="The A-Spire" href="places\the-a-spire.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The A-Spire</a> is hardened and air-gapped; it has its own on-site power generation, a combination of fusion and aerostat. We also want to limit civilian casualties; most of the people working there don’t have a choice. We’re the distraction team; Black’s team will do the primary infiltration.<br>People are reluctant to talk about the Pyramid, and for good reason, but Annika has her ways. Compromising the staff isn’t going to happen; they’re all junkies, addicted to substances they get as part of their employment, and the Moderns have ways of keeping them on the hook. It’s a combination of drugs, conditioning, etc. There’s a generalized drug distribution system—aerosols—that’s the pharma equivalent of MSG. It makes everything more effective. They have their own hospital inside. The aerosol system is highly secured, and Vasser will sometimes just fuck with it for fun.<br>Security depends entirely on how much you’re paying. Everyone gets an RFID chip, so they can track you. The guards are universally enhanced: chrome, bio, a combination of both. There’s even a few amps on staff—their identities are kept carefully secret.<br>Annika has an idea: the Pyramid regularly hires bands to perform. Annika calls up her old band; they could be our way in. Between the band and the dancers, we can create a distraction. Moto can spoof the RFID chips. It’s also rumored that the Moderns have the capability to cause everybody in areas that they control to go berserk—and even direct them.<br>We decide we’re going to have to go into the public areas, see what we can find out.]]></description><link>operations\collision-part-7.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Operations/Collision - Part 7.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 01:07:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[July 4, 2176]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br><br>We get an interview with <a data-href="Marinela Stanciu" href="people\marinela-stanciu.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Marinela Stanciu</a>, events coordinator for <a data-href="The A-Spire" href="places\the-a-spire.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The A-Spire</a>. She wants to know what Non-Binary Riot’s musical philosophy.<br>They have another artist—very popular—known as <a data-href="Vox-D" href="people\vox-d.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Vox-D</a>. He’s a dedicated artist—lives for the music—but his music is described as inhuman—maybe even anti-human. Despite that, he has no chrome. Marinela suggests a ‘Battle of the Bands’. Annika notes that both she and Vox-D don’t have chrome, and Stanciu jumps on that with a smirk. She then asks if Annika has anyone particularly flashy in the group—Annika gives a passionate response about how punk isn’t about looking punk, but to protest the status quo and inspire people.<br>Vox-D’s bodyguard is Miko Shade; she’s a chrome supremacist who likes throwing her power around.<br>We go to consult with Vox on security measures; when we get to his suite, he’s in the middle of a column of synth gear, and the way he’s playing it, he’s very clearly on some high-octane pharmaceutical. He’s lucid enough, though, and when Gloria brings up the question of stage security, it’s notable that Shade’s nowhere around. Vox says Shade’s mostly around for the opportunity to fuck people up. True to his nihilist philosophy, Vox says not to bother with securing his performance—he doesn’t matter, we don’t matter, and none of it matters. The machine’s going to eat us all one day anyway.<br>His music is screaming cacophony, but it still grabs the audience on a gut-deep level. He’s definitely sharing the emptiness inside him with his audience, whether they like it or not.<br>He does warn us about a ‘prick’ running along this level calling himself ‘<a data-href="Lucky 13" href="people\lucky-13.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Lucky 13</a>’, who’s a rich kid that thinks he’s hardcore. We spot him at a distance—he’s hard to miss.<br>There’s a group of four young women across from Lucky 13 who are looking extremely bored with his antics; three of them are simply trying to ignore the boors. In another corner is an older man with an air of calm authority, whose uniform bears the logo of the Pan-Corporate Authority. Their diplomats are well-known for being nano-wired for diplomacy.<br>Lucky 13 is making noise, announcing himself in the third person, bothering the other women—one of the women, the one with the media equipment—makes a call. A few moments later, a couple members of the Modern security team come in. Lucky 13’s ignored at least one incoming call. Security asks him politely to come with them, as he’s causing a disruption, and Lucky 13 refuses. Expertly, one of the security types dodges past his hostile entourage and hits him with something—Neocan, aka “Flush”. It’s an advanced med that flushes out pharmaceuticals from someone’s body. It’s a hard come-down, and he immediately starts complaining that he isn’t able to party during his enforced sobriety. Lucky 13 demands a manager, and Gloria steps in. She doesn’t lie, exactly; all she says is that she ‘manages’ things.<br>Another voice speaks up. “Excuse me, Mr. Nathaniel Bancroft-Jameson the 13th.” The speaker seems to have practically appeared from one of the staff entrances. “My name is Darius Vasser. I happen to own this establishment.” The Bancroft-Jamesons are in tight with <a data-href="Dallas Dynamics" href="factions\dallas-dynamics.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dallas Dynamics</a>; they’re part of the northern end of the Corridor. Children of corporate privilege; the offspring and by-blows, the genetically-cleaned spawn of Dallas Dynamics.<br>Fortunately, Jameson isn’t going to be stupid—at least not in front of Vasser. Vasser turns and nods at the bartenders, and everyone’s given a free meal and free drinks for the night.<br>Vasser then turns to the primary in the small group of women, who goes in a moment from being bored to being utterly entrancing. “Ms. Strand, we’re so pleased to have you in the A-Spire.” Strand calls him by his first name; he doesn’t seem displeased. And, as if to complete the contrast with Jameson, there is an intense intelligence in her eyes. <br>Vasser then turns to us. It’s a little spooky how he knows Annika’s public persona; he makes sure to try to upsell her on marketing services.<br>We agree that Vasser is one creepy guy—and that he’d probably order an execution in exactly the same voice as he said hello.<br><br>Deep in the complex, the holiest of holies: the AI core. There’s Darius. He’s looking up at an image generated by the core itself, wreathed in cooling mist, and holograms that look simple, but at a closer look would be nothing but high-end data. The crystalline matrix of the AI has been altered to look like a throne—and it is not empty. “You realize,” says the figure seated on the throne, towering above Vasser, “that something is going to happen. The Church is moving against you.”<br>“Tell me something I don’t know.”<br>“I already told you. I don’t see the future—that is beyond me. But, I can tell you I’m almost done compiling the codes. It’s a fascinating construct. I believe the revelation of it—at the climax of the quadcentennial celebration here-will be a momentous event. You’re going to change the world, Darius. And some people aren’t going to like that at all.”<br>“Show me the current compilation!” Darius snaps impatiently.<br>"I am not your servant. I am your partner in this. The potential for disruption of the Church of the Cyberpapacy is immense.”<br>An image starts to form out of all the data hovering in the mist. At first, it looks like a city; it could be any city… and then the city elements start falling away from it, revealing what look like foothills, and a vast structure atop them. It’s the Promised Land, at the heart of the GodNet. “At the climax, as you wish, we will introduce the Faithful to a new form of worship. Our form.”]]></description><link>operations\collision-the-a-spire-job-part-1.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Operations/Collision - The A-Spire Job - Part 1.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 01:48:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[July 4, 2176]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br><br>Vasser is planning something big for the finale; he isn’t saying what, but he plans to go not just national but international. Our concert and the infiltration is tomorrow; we’ve got some time, so we spread out and do some investigation.<br>Calamity goes to mingle among the race crews; Crasher, in the parkour contest, is said to be sponsored by the Moderns; that would theoretically give him an edge, but something’s got him very nervous. He’s been hanging around the high point on the track. (High enough that someone there could see inside the performance center.)<br>Attica goes ahead and signs up for the parkour race; taking a look from the upper vantage point, she can see easily into the stadium and the Spire itself. Crasher’s supposed to be enhanced to the gills; he’s definitely got some reflex-ware of some sort. He’s also looking at specific areas on the arena and the Spire. Kes does some calling around, and Crasher’s got a mix of augs that are highly unstable and require constant maintenance and needs a lot more maintenance drugs. He’d have had to do some high-powered jobs to afford those meds. Like, perhaps, contract killing? It certainly looks like he’s scoping out the VIP quarters…]]></description><link>operations\collision-the-a-spire-job-part-2.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Operations/Collision - The A-Spire Job - Part 2.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 01:48:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[July 4, 2176]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br><br>We do our final preparations. Most of the team’s doing security for the concert; Firefox, of course, is leading the band, and Attica (with Graves as support) is running the Human Race in a bid to keep Crasher from killing whoever he means to kill.<br>Darius is exhorting the quadricentennial, and promising a big surprise, while the Cyberpapacy blimp hovers overhead broadcasting religious music and reminders that we are all sinners.<br>The Human Race kicks off with a bang! Crasher and Eris take the lead, followed by Attica, with the other competitors getting a slower start. Firefox is slightly ahead in the Battle of the Bands, but Vox D is putting up a fight!  Spider, working security, spots someone lurking at the concert; he’s well-dressed, in flashy clothes, but somehow manages to evade notice. She intercepts the guy; he acts like he can’t hear Spider’s polite inquiry. Kes notices that this guy has friends—clearly operators, as opposed to the drugged-up music enthusiasts.<br>Attica and the other leaders get slowed down by the electrical field; it’s less a danger than an annoyance, and that allows the rest of the racers to catch up. Firefox is successfully keeping the crowd upbeat, and it looks like the agitators aren’t too happy about that. They’re only observing at this point… They’re blending in color-wise, but the cut of their clothes is much more conservative. Realizing that lets the team spot the agitators better. …and then there’s the guy with the hologram for a head. He’s a Tombs music producer by the name of Quill DeWitt; he’s a risk-taker, amiably scummy. He plays a lot more low-class than he really is. More to the point, he’s not in the Modern’s pockets. He doesn’t have a head anymore; the Moderns lopped it off.<br>As the pack approaches the highest point of the track, Crasher is in the lead, but not by much. Vox D isn’t really throwing down the hard diss tracks, which is driving the event coordinator crazy. “Get that asshole under control,” she mutters.<br>Infobox
<img alt="cover hsmall" src="lib\media\cyberpapacy-cufflink.png">
<br>Gloria notices that the agitators are moving in a precise pattern, scoping out where everyone is. Calamity notices that one of them is, indeed, wearing a cufflink marking them as Cyberpapacy. Firefox, with a fireball kiss, gives a special shout-out to the Cyberpapacy agitators in the audience; Vox D is working with Attica to keep the crowd going. The Church rhetoric outside grows ever more fervent as the clock ticks closer to…<br>MIDNIGHT. Fireworks go off, holographic displays… the tension in the crowd redoubles. Something is definitely imminent… Calamity notices that the Church jackpriests and their goons are set up for riot control. Darius is announcing the quadricentennial: “Ladies and gentlemen and others—especially our others—they tell you to hate yourselves, to follow their synthetic god… Tonight, I, We, the Spirit Moderns, offer you an option! They talk about a digital afterlife, I offer you a Digital Now!”<br>On the racetrack, Crusher puts on the speed and passes Attica, reaching the point. His arm reconfigures itself into a weapon; Attica draws and fires, trying to spoil his aim. It’s not enough; Crusher fires. The bullet pierces the spire… and Crusher starts swearing. His arm’s overloading.<br>The guy Spider tagged steps out of his holographic disguise (his “confessional”), and is revealed to be Father Vladyslav László. “Friends, do not be deceived!” he holds out his hands and implores.<br>“The fuck is this, battle of the Bishops?” Firefox growls.<br>Outside, alarms are going off. The propaganda zep has crossed into the Modern’s airspace; the holoscreens on the side come down, and it’s full of troopships. The hologram on the side of the zep reads:<br><img alt="prometheus message.png" src="lib\media\prometheus-message.png">]]></description><link>operations\collision-the-a-spire-job-part-3.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Operations/Collision - The A-Spire Job - Part 3.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 02:58:49 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\cyberpapacy-cufflink.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\cyberpapacy-cufflink.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[March 24, 2176]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br>There’s a number of interesting jobs out there, but the one we decide to go for is another one from <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Zero Ballard" data-href="Zero Ballard" href="people\zero-ballard.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Trust</a>: an extraction, of <a data-href="Terra McAllister" href="people\terra-mcallister.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Terra McAllister</a>. McAllister got a message to Ballard; she indicated she’d voluntarily remanded herself into their custody, and now they don’t want to let her go.<br>He says getting in to where she’s being held will be reasonably easy; getting her out will be more difficult. She’s currently in the hands of <a data-href="Cascadia Pro-Cop" href="factions\cascadia-pro-cop.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Cascadia Pro-Cop</a>. It’s possible we’ll be able to extract her simply by waving some Wu around; Ballard’s not sure why exactly she’s in custody. She’s not at CPC headquarters; she’s been moved to a Pro-Cop black site. Ballard doesn’t know where the site is.<br>He suspects it’s near the HQ—somewhere near <a data-href="Bryker Woods" href="places\bryker-woods.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Bryker Woods</a>, part of <a data-href="Old West (Austex West)" href="places\old-west-(austex-west).html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Old West (Austex West)</a> Austin. The most likely possibility is right across the street, in an old building that used to be a state agency. The on-site security detachment is probably fairly small, since the HQ is available for fast reinforcement.<br>Attica gets herself inside as a temp worker, and the rest of the team observes from the outside. After a week’s worth of observation, the team manages to locate the tunnel between the HQ and the black site: right under the wall, parallel to the MoPac Transit Tunnel.<br><br><br>Attica overhears some of the cops talking about how they take overflow from HQ. When they want to interrogate people, they use VR. Also gets the name of the captain that runs the interrogations: Captain <a data-href="Quinn Jackstadt" href="people\quinn-jackstadt.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Quinn Jackstadt</a>.<br>It’s Graves that figures out where to look: the shower area, and Attica confirms it: a swing-down staircase that leads to something called Sector Five. We don’t yet know what it looks like, only that it’s underground and it’s guarded by sentry guns. The guards have IFF tags that let them pass. The sentry guns aren’t controlled from HQ; HQ can lock down the exit, but the guns are the responsibility of the black site.<br>The first password Moto creates triggers a security alert, and Pro-Cop is on edge. They’re expecting to be hit by the Hammers. And, learning from the mistake, Moto manages to make two much, much better passes; one for Attica and once for the evac team. It’s obvious why the Hammers would be getting ready to hit Pro-Cop; they’re going after McAllister. Graves does some info-digging, and finds out that <a data-href="Zoey Belmont" href="people\zoey-belmont.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Zoey Belmont</a> is also sniffing around. Belmont was the source of one of the jobs offered to us: looking for muscle for a snatch-and-grab. Her target is one of the top contenders for the top spot among the Panzers: <a data-href="Lucas Konstantin" href="people\lucas-konstantin.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Lucas Konstantin</a>.<br>We tentatively plan to extract McAllister during the Hammer attack; in order to do that, it would help if we can sow some more chaos amongst the Hammers… we contact Belmont, offering our assistance with the Konstantin extraction. She offers his dossier, and notes that while we’re setting that up, she has a second extraction job waiting in the wings: <a data-href="Dr. Su Xinyi Zheng" href="people\dr.-su-xinyi-zheng.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dr. Su Xinyi Zheng</a>.]]></description><link>operations\slings-and-arrows-part-1.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Operations/Slings and Arrows - Part 1.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 04:00:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[April 1, 2176]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br>After some discussion, we conclude that letting the <a data-href="Panzer Hammers" href="factions\panzer-hammers.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Panzer Hammers</a> let loose with their attack isn’t a good idea. Best way to handle things is to go forward with the Konstantin extraction. Graves contacts a friend of his for some additional firepower: <a data-href="Annika Lovelace" href="characters\annika-lovelace.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Annika Lovelace</a>. She agrees in exchange for some help with a personal problem.<br><a data-href="Lucas Konstantin" href="people\lucas-konstantin.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Lucas Konstantin</a>’s a greasy, paranoid son of a bitch. He hangs out at—and may be part-owner of—a vet bar called Bogey. Its symbol is the bogey on a tank; it’s a vet bar. Being a vet bar, it’s kind of insular; on the other hand, one of us is a vet. It’s not specifically a tanker bar, but it caters to them a little bit. Most of the local joygirls avoid the place; it’s all gangoons all the time. It’s the Panzer’s little clubhouse, complete with rooms for them to sleep it off.<br>Moto manages to tap into all the old copper laying under the black site, dating hundreds of years back to when the site was a State of Texas worksite.<br><br><br>We hit Bogey. The area around it’s surrounded by mines, and they’ve got a milspec high-band antenna on the roof. This isn’t their main base, just an outpost, but it’s a whole lot tougher a nut than we initially expected. The money gone into this suggests corpo involvement.<br>Attica helps talk George up to the antenna, and Moto’s able to tap into their comms. Beneath the camo tarps, there’s an assault aerodyne and a battle truck—a mobile command post. We’re able to use the storm sewers beneath to get into the bar beneath the sight of the Nazis. While we’re moving into position, Moto gets into the bar’s security system. He gets eyes on Konstantin—he’s upstairs, in a room, with <a data-href="Verner Jackstadt" href="people\verner-jackstadt.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Verner Jackstadt</a>.  And they’re on the phone with someone; Moto manages to eavesdrop on the call. <br>“Konstantin, I need you to do what we agreed on,” says the man on the other end. Moto identifies the man as <a data-href="Osric Kayne" href="people\osric-kayne.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Osric Kayne</a>, a member of the <a data-href="AusTex City Development Council" href="AusTex City Development Council" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">AusTex City Development Council</a>. He’s provided the Panzers the gear as part of an unholy union between Ms. Suvov with <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Koizumi Aerospace Corporation" data-href="Koizumi Aerospace Corporation" href="factions\koizumi-aerospace-corporation.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Koizumi Aerospace</a> and AusTex. “I said I cannot and will not authorize and condone you rampaging from Bryker Woods through Military Heights to execute a jailbreak, I don’t care how valuable the target is. I am trying to negotiate.” Kayne’s plan is to have the Panzers clear everyone out to make room for a Koizumi manufacturing plant—specifically, one across from the Tesla Gigafactory. “Need I remind you, Verner, that we agreed to provide you with those resources to take care of the Vampire Nation, not to attack a duly bonded security company!”<br>Verner sounds bored. “Ja ja, we will do that, but my people are getting very impatient about Ms. McAllister. We will brook no further delay; you have 24 hours. Goodbye.”<br>That’s our cue to move. Spider takes two of the external guards out. Attica goes up into the ceiling; she doesn’t quite manage to grapple-kill the guard, but he panics and starts spraying bullets around. The Nazis are shocked; it gives us a precious moment of surprise. Attica takes out the netrunner; Gloria blows the rear axle of the battle truck into oblivion. Meanwhile, Annika sows discord in the form of a powerful wave of homoerotic attraction in the middle of a Nazi bar. Graves blows another Nazi all over his console, and Spider’s knives teach the panicked guard how to accessorize with his own blood.<br>The Nazis on the first floor run. Unfortunately for them, Moto changed the IFF on the mines… and their getaway becomes explosive. We manage to take Konstantin, though Verner gets away, both men threatening vengeance.<br>Belmont’s positively ecstatic. We managed to pull it off without any official heat, though the Panzers are now our mortal enemies. ]]></description><link>operations\slings-and-arrows-part-2.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Operations/Slings and Arrows - Part 2.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 04:20:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[April 6, 2176]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br>Final preparations are made, and we decide to sneak in through the tunnel from the abandoned admin complex. It comes out in a maintenance area beneath the airpad. Moto does his magic on the computer systems, pulling up the cameras on the maintenance area. He registers three clear heat signatures, and two more stealthed on the catwalk. <br>Attica sneaks forward to eavesdrop. The two on the catwalk are <a data-href="Quinn Jackstadt" href="people\quinn-jackstadt.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Quinn Jackstadt</a> and <a data-href="Isis Wakeman" href="people\isis-wakeman.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Isis Wakeman</a>; they’re arguing about an “upgrade” to the site’s defenses. Turns out they have something called an Eversor Walker—a light assault mech. It’s a bullet hose. Quinn’s pissed about it being there; since the Panzers are no longer going to be conducting their assault, there’s no reason for it to be there. (Quinn’s also not real happy about being in charge of the black site.)  The new construction we were worried about is apparently its storage facility.<br>To get to Sector Five, we need a small distraction; Moto brings up a small roach drone and starts fiddling with the VTOL. It starts making some very unpleasant sounding noises, like it’s got the electronic equivalent of epilepsy. That distracts the mechanics enough for us to sneak across to the Sector Five entrance…<br>We use our shiny fake passcards to get past the security booth when Moto pings us urgently. “Guys? Guys… they’ve rotated the keys…” Moto works fast to secure the turrets—just in case—while Firefox and Graves talk us through the gates. A coincidental? system malfunction works in our favor, and the security guards buy it. We’re waved on through; Moto’s still got control of the systems, and after a database search to locate our target, we move.<br>Unfortunately, there’s no predicting the human element. A cop steps out of the security office—the name of ‘Keefe’ on his uniform—and on seeing us, he steps back into the office. Alarms start going off. Graves flings a canister of crash foam at the office door, blocking it; Attica manages to break the electromagnetic lock into the VR cell block. Moto tries to make it look like a false alarm, but the cops aren’t buying it. Graves dashes down to jack in and start the wake-up process, while Attica jams the northern door. Calamity hears Jackstadt coming, and warns us in time for Moto to prevent them from locking down the elevator. Whoever’s on the northern door is about to break through; Firefox manages to weld it shut, while Attica heads to the other end of the corridor, tossing a gas grenade. Unfortunately, the first two responders have breathers and aren’t affected; they come out of the gas and hose Attica and Calamity down! Two more guards come out on the first floor, spotting Graves. Kestrel does her medical magic to jumpstart McAllister’s waking process.<br>Graves starts jacking out as Firefox steps out on the catwalk and lights on fire, snarling, “If you don’t want to get burned, get out of the way!” They don’t run, surprisingly; they start yelling “AMP! AMP!" They pull back, but in good order. Moto gives us our exit directions; Attica jams the sliding door between them and the oncoming Response team. Calamity takes one of Attica’s smoke grenades and tries to toss it down the corridor; it bounces and goes off… elsewhere.<br>One of their bots comes charging up, slamming into the jammed door; it doesn’t knock it down, but the grate is now a tangled mess.  The heavy weapons guy readies to fire HE on the door, while downstairs the response team rolls a SLAG grenade through the door. Moto opens the doors between us and the pad, and we begin a fighting retreat. Jackstadt’s directing an attempted intercept, while Pro-Cop’s own Amp throws a telekinetic bomb our way. We throw a little more crash foam for protection and make a break, as Moto seals the doors along the response team’s route. There’s still cops along our exit route, though, and they start shooting! It’s a clean miss, though—and Spider doesn’t give them a second chance! She rips through one of them, leaving him bleeding out, while Gloria rampages behind her—the remaining cops scatter while Attica seals the door behind us!<br>There’s only one obstacle left: the mech. George distracts it long enough for us to lay down Attica’s last two smoke grenades, and we make a run for the tunnel. The mech’s barely small enough to fit in the tunnel behind us—it simply lays down fire. It’s not terribly accurate; a few of us take some fragments, and Graves drops his last crash foam canister. We make it to Torrent without further damage, as George joins us. Calamity’s usual skill behind the wheel gets us out and merged into traffic, where we simply disappear.]]></description><link>operations\slings-and-arrows-part-3.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Operations/Slings and Arrows - Part 3.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 04:18:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Abel Kane]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

<img alt="cover hmed" src="lib\media\abel-kane.png"><br>
AusTex Social Services
<br>Veteran of the 181st Shock Battalion, off-world shock trooper. Tough as hull steel, smart enough to get out before he went nuts, and not someone to fuck with.<br>Kane “got tired of shooting women and children—pretty much day one.”]]></description><link>people\abel-kane.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">People/Abel Kane.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 02:03:29 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\abel-kane.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\abel-kane.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Aidan Graves]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

<img alt="cover hmed" src="lib\media\aidan-graves.png"><br>
Fist Against the Man
<br><br><a data-href="Nubotica" href="Nubotica" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Nubotica</a> w/ Biocapacitors<br>Cybernetic Infrastructure Baseline<br>
Emergency Stabilization Factor<br>Cranial Jack<br>
Active Sense Processor<br>
Gunlink<br>
Syntheye Mods (Impostor, I/R, Tactical, Zoom)<br>
Sensory Recorder<br>Caption
<img alt="hsmall" src="lib\media\graves'-rose-.72-heavy-pistol.png"><br>
Graves’ .72 Heavy Pistol
]]></description><link>people\aidan-graves.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">People/Aidan Graves.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 03:01:50 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\aidan-graves.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\aidan-graves.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Angel Rivera]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

“img.png” could not be found.<br>
Extra Info
<br>Angel Rivera is an Experienced vehicle mechanic with a small shop in The Tomb. Lanky guy with shaggy brown hair, sort of clumsy and awkward but knows his way around cars. <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Violet Moore" data-href="Violet Moore" href="characters\violet-moore.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Calamity</a> and Angel go waaay back; a fixer sent her to his shop after a particularly nasty job that messed up ol' Torrent's chassis. Angel think's Calamity is good company, or maybe a lucky charm. She thinks he's maybe got a bolt loose but he swears things started going better for him after they met.]]></description><link>people\angel-rivera.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">People/Angel Rivera.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 16:24:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Artemis Sonata]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

<img alt="cover hmed" src="lib\media\artemis-sonata.png"><br>
Rocker With a Cause
<br>Very popular rocker from Boston. Anti-corp, anti-Church, and her music is both very popular and highly resented by various factions because of that.]]></description><link>people\artemis-sonata.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">People/Artemis Sonata.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 02:25:44 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\artemis-sonata.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\artemis-sonata.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bishop Silvestr Devin]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

<img alt="cover hmed" src="lib\media\silvestr-devin.png"><br>
Militant Bishop of the Cyberpapacy
<br>Former member of a PMC, early adopter of the Cyberpapacy. Zealous, militant, but highly status-conscious.]]></description><link>people\bishop-silvestr-devin.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">People/Bishop Silvestr Devin.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 03:26:16 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\silvestr-devin.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\silvestr-devin.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cadence Flux]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

<img alt="cover hsmall" src="lib\media\cadence-flux.png"><br>
Independent fixer
]]></description><link>people\cadence-flux.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">People/Cadence Flux.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 01:52:28 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\cadence-flux.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\cadence-flux.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Darius Vasser]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

<img alt="cover hsmall" src="lib\media\darius-vasser.png"><br>
The Boss of the Spirit Moderns
]]></description><link>people\darius-vasser.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">People/Darius Vasser.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 02:28:31 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\darius-vasser.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\darius-vasser.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Daron Ocano]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

<img alt="cover hmed" src="lib\media\daron-ocano.png"><br>
Neurosoft Enthusiast
<br>He’s got a whole lot of ATR tags: mostly drug offenses.<br>Working for Verner Jackstadt.]]></description><link>people\daron-ocano.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">People/Daron Ocano.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 03:07:37 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\daron-ocano.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\daron-ocano.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Delia Graydon]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

<img alt="cover hmed" src="lib\media\delia-graydon.png"><br>
Spirit Moderns Gun Thug
<br>Many people think that she’s not real bright because of how she dresses, but she’s actually a sharp and deadly operator.<br><img alt="Dog Girl.png" src="lib\media\dog-girl.png">]]></description><link>people\delia-graydon.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">People/Delia Graydon.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 03:59:35 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\delia-graydon.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\delia-graydon.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Dr. Narindar Nwolko]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

<img alt="cover hmed" src="lib\media\dr.-narindar-nwolko.png"><br>
Extra Info
<br>Cyber-doc to the corporate aristos, not well-liked outside the corporate enclaves. He’s a snooty surgeon, one of the “I am god” types.<br>He’s also almost good enough to justify the attitude. He’s known for being one of the go-to guys for doing off-the-books blackjack installs: top-tier, military-grade cybernetics. Not part of his ‘normal’ job, but he can charge premium prices for things you usually can’t get.<br><br><img alt="Nwolkos Clinic.png" src="lib\media\nwolkos-clinic.png" style="width: 400px; max-width: 100%;">]]></description><link>people\dr.-narindar-nwolko.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">People/Dr. Narindar Nwolko.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 02:29:22 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\dr.-narindar-nwolko.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\dr.-narindar-nwolko.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Dr. Poirot]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

<img alt="cover hmed" src="lib\media\dr.-poirot.png"><br>
Church Heretic
]]></description><link>people\dr.-poirot.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">People/Dr. Poirot.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 01:43:14 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\dr.-poirot.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\dr.-poirot.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Dr. Skin]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

<img alt="cover hmed" src="lib\media\dr.-skin-full.png"><br>
Freaky Ripperdoc
<br>A ripperdoc that’s about as shady as they come. Skin stays alive because of the exotics community—they’ll do mods that no one else will touch. They work with scavs and gangers to get the parts—no questions asked. Not only that, but Skin changes their appearance on the regular. Makes it difficult to know who you’re dealing with. Kestrel’s familiar with them; they like to maximize their profits.]]></description><link>people\dr.-skin.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">People/Dr. Skin.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 03:03:28 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\dr.-skin-full.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\dr.-skin-full.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Dr. Su Xinyi Zheng]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

<img alt="cover hmed" src="lib\media\dr.-su-xinyi-zheng.png"><br>
Lead Researcher, Waring-Erikson Technology Group
]]></description><link>people\dr.-su-xinyi-zheng.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">People/Dr. Su Xinyi Zheng.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 02:27:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\dr.-su-xinyi-zheng.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\dr.-su-xinyi-zheng.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Earl Blank]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

<img alt="cover hmed" src="lib\media\earl-blank.png"><br>
Independent Nation-State
<br>Specializes in intrusion tech, veteran of one of the innumerable brushfire conflicts. Absolutely trustworthy. He sticks to the spirit of a deal. Earl is absolutely reliable, and people like working with him. Might help that he’s a huge dude, and is registered as an independent nation-state.]]></description><link>people\earl-blank.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">People/Earl Blank.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 16:25:50 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\earl-blank.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\earl-blank.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Enzo Blackford]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

<img alt="cover hmed" src="lib\media\enzo-blackford.png"><br>
Extra Info
<br>The kind of guy who knows he’s the smartest guy in the room, and he wants everyone to know it. Cybersecurity chief for the Moderns.]]></description><link>people\enzo-blackford.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">People/Enzo Blackford.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 02:00:59 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\enzo-blackford.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\enzo-blackford.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Henry Jericho]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

<img alt="cover hmed" src="lib\media\henry-jericho.png"><br>
Family Guy
<br>Henry’s a family guy; the flow says that he's got someone in his extended family who's in deep deep shit. Henry, so the rumor says, is also hooked on <a data-href="Narcosoft" href="Narcosoft" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Narcosoft</a>.<br>He’s getting a little squirrelly; either his addiction’s getting worse or word’s getting around.<br>Sometime around June of 2176, Henry’s problems catch up with him and he and his family disappear.]]></description><link>people\henry-jericho.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">People/Henry Jericho.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 01:51:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\henry-jericho.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\henry-jericho.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hospitaller-Captain Adam Zimmerman]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

<img alt="cover hmed" src="lib\media\adam-zimmerman.png"><br>
Gifted Captain of the Hospitallers
]]></description><link>people\hospitaller-captain-adam-zimmerman.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">People/Hospitaller-Captain Adam Zimmerman.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 04:04:10 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\adam-zimmerman.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\adam-zimmerman.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Isis Wakeman]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

“img.png” could not be found.<br>
Extra Info
<br>VP of operations]]></description><link>people\isis-wakeman.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">People/Isis Wakeman.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 03:31:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jan de Ven]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

<img alt="cover hmed" src="lib\media\jan-de-ven.png"><br>
Combat Zone Medic
]]></description><link>people\jan-de-ven.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">People/Jan de Ven.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 03:02:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\jan-de-ven.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\jan-de-ven.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lloyd Ashworth]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

<img alt="cover hmed" src="lib\media\lloyd-ashworth.png"><br>
Crazy Lloyd
<br>Lloyd is a war veteran. Rumor has it he was the subject of enhancement experiments—biotechnical. He’s not a bad man; he just has a temper. An explosive temper.]]></description><link>people\lloyd-ashworth.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">People/Lloyd Ashworth.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 04:03:31 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\lloyd-ashworth.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\lloyd-ashworth.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lucas Konstantin]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

<img alt="cover hmed" src="lib\media\lucas-konstantin.png"><br>
Extra Info
<br>Lucas goes for the neuralware rather than the overt chrome, and he’s professionally paranoid. He used to be an elite tanker, the tanker version of Special Forces. Offworld veteran.<br>Handed over to Zoey Belmont; current status unclear.]]></description><link>people\lucas-konstantin.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">People/Lucas Konstantin.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 02:25:29 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\lucas-konstantin.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\lucas-konstantin.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lucky 13]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

<img alt="cover hmed" src="lib\media\lucky-13-and-entourage.png"><br>
Rich Kid Playing Tough
]]></description><link>people\lucky-13.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">People/Lucky 13.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 02:13:45 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\lucky-13-and-entourage.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\lucky-13-and-entourage.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Marinela Stanciu]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

<img alt="cover hmed" src="lib\media\marinela-stanciu.png"><br>
A-Spire Events Coordinator
]]></description><link>people\marinela-stanciu.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">People/Marinela Stanciu.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 01:29:59 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\marinela-stanciu.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\marinela-stanciu.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mittens]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

<img alt="cover hmed" src="lib\media\mittens.png"><br>
Feline Scientist
<br>Mittens is a <a data-href="Cybrid" href="setting\cybrid.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Cybrid</a>. She’s a lab assistant looking to recover her human.]]></description><link>people\mittens.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">People/Mittens.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 04:30:42 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\mittens.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\mittens.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Nastasia Gwinelle]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

<img alt="cover hmed" src="lib\media\nastasia-gwinelle.png"><br>
Prince of the Vampire Nation
]]></description><link>people\nastasia-gwinelle.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">People/Nastasia Gwinelle.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 03:03:08 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\nastasia-gwinelle.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\nastasia-gwinelle.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[October Tallisi]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

<img alt="cover hmed" src="lib\media\october-tallisi.png"><br>
Discount Prices
<br>Rich kid, works for <a data-href="Zero Ballard" href="people\zero-ballard.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Zero Ballard</a> but is always trying to one-up him. He's got an attitude, and he hangs out with the Vampire Nation. Style over substance.]]></description><link>people\october-tallisi.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">People/October Tallisi.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 04:18:29 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\october-tallisi.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\october-tallisi.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Oliver Gaskell]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

<img alt="cover hmed" src="lib\media\oliver-gaskell.png"><br>
Extra Info
<br>Ex-con. Irish mobster, spent time in Huntsville. Hard-core.]]></description><link>people\oliver-gaskell.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">People/Oliver Gaskell.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 03:28:58 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\oliver-gaskell.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\oliver-gaskell.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Quinn Jackstadt]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

<img alt="cover hmed" src="lib\media\quinn-jackstadt.png"><br>
Captain, Cascadia Pro-Cop
<br>Brother to <a data-href="Verner Jackstadt" href="people\verner-jackstadt.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Verner Jackstadt</a>. Like his brother, started out in the military; unlike his brother, went for the corpo cop rather than the fascist gang. Not on good terms with Verner. Constantly having to prove he’s not simping for his brother.]]></description><link>people\quinn-jackstadt.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">People/Quinn Jackstadt.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 03:10:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\quinn-jackstadt.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\quinn-jackstadt.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Reality Black]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

<img alt="cover hmed" src="lib\media\reality-black.png"><br>
Rockergirl
]]></description><link>people\reality-black.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">People/Reality Black.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 01:53:27 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\reality-black.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\reality-black.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Simone Church]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

<img alt="cover hmed" src="lib\media\simone-church.png"><br>
Escapee from the Order of Hospitallers
]]></description><link>people\simone-church.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">People/Simone Church.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 02:59:39 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\simone-church.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\simone-church.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sistrix Radoslava Barsamian]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

<img alt="cover hmed" src="lib\media\sistrix-radoslava-barsamian.png"><br>
Investigator of the Order of St. Michael
]]></description><link>people\sistrix-radoslava-barsamian.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">People/Sistrix Radoslava Barsamian.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 04:01:37 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\sistrix-radoslava-barsamian.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\sistrix-radoslava-barsamian.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Skinjob Records]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

<img alt="cover hmed" src="lib\media\crystal-green.png"><br>
Co-Owner of Skinjob Records
<br>Infobox

<img alt="cover hmed" src="lib\media\greezy-trillion.jpg"><br>
Co-Owner of Skinjob Records
]]></description><link>people\skinjob-records.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">People/Skinjob Records.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 02:16:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\crystal-green.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\crystal-green.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tanit Saad]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

<img alt="cover hmed" src="lib\media\tanit-saad.png"><br>
”Ex” Wutani Agent
]]></description><link>people\tanit-saad.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">People/Tanit Saad.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 02:42:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\tanit-saad.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\tanit-saad.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Terra McAllister]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

<img alt="cover hmed" src="lib\media\terra-mcallister.png"><br>
Corporate Thief
<br>Worked a science lab down in <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Weirdsville (Austex Corridor South)" data-href="Weirdsville (Austex Corridor South)" href="places\weirdsville-(austex-corridor-south).html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Weirdsville</a> before she stole some code from <a data-href="Waring-Erikson Technology Group" href="factions\waring-erikson-technology-group.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Waring-Erikson Technology Group</a>.]]></description><link>people\terra-mcallister.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">People/Terra McAllister.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 01:14:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\terra-mcallister.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\terra-mcallister.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Erinye]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

<img alt="cover hsmall" src="lib\media\the-erinye.png"><br>
The Circuit
<br>Fixer for <a data-href="The Circuit" href="factions\the-circuit.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Circuit</a>. Based in the <a data-href="Grand Metropol Hotel" href="places\grand-metropol-hotel.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Grand Metropol Hotel</a>.]]></description><link>people\the-erinye.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">People/The Erinye.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 03:39:33 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\the-erinye.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\the-erinye.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Verner Jackstadt]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

<img alt="cover hmed" src="lib\media\verner-jackstadt.png"><br>
Big-Ass Cyborg
<br>A former member of the <a data-href="Panzer Hammers" href="factions\panzer-hammers.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Panzer Hammers</a>, he got ousted when his boss got wasted. He’s got ATR flags popping up all over the place.<br>Probably called in the hit job on the executive client of <a data-href="Dr. Narindar Nwolko" href="people\dr.-narindar-nwolko.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dr. Narindar Nwolko</a>.<br>Caption
<img alt="hsmall" src="lib\media\verner's-arm.png"><br>
Verner’s Arm
]]></description><link>people\verner-jackstadt.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">People/Verner Jackstadt.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 02:40:47 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\verner-jackstadt.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\verner-jackstadt.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Vox-D]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

<img alt="cover hmed" src="lib\media\vox-d.png"><br>
Unchromed Musician with a Bent for Antihuman Music
<br>Vox-D is very popular with churchgoers, but he’s not exactly approved. The message that to thrive, people must become more inhuman seems on the surface to be anti-Church, but it could be spun to be a deeper Church mystery if need be. He’s a nihilist, or portrays himself as such.<br>He does appear to be genuine about his art; he’s making plenty of money, but it doesn’t seem to be about the money so much as the message. And it’s not likely he’s a willing or witting pawn of the Church.]]></description><link>people\vox-d.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">People/Vox-D.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 01:57:05 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\vox-d.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\vox-d.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Wynston Lien]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

<img alt="cover hmed" src="lib\media\wynston-lien.png"><br>
Cybervice dealer
<br>A man of no redeeming qualities, he’s a coward, a liar, a pimp, and would sell out his own grandmother for a wu.]]></description><link>people\wynston-lien.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">People/Wynston Lien.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 02:24:16 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\wynston-lien.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\wynston-lien.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Zero Ballard]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

<img alt="cover hmed" src="lib\media\zero-ballard.png"><br>
The Trust
<br>He looks corporate, but he’s street all the way. Goes to great lengths to make sure the deals he makes are fair and the people he works with are trustworthy.<br>Is having a lot of trouble keeping his face, <a data-href="October Tallisi" href="people\october-tallisi.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">October Tallisi</a>, in line.]]></description><link>people\zero-ballard.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">People/Zero Ballard.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 04:19:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\zero-ballard.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\zero-ballard.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Zina Kova]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

<img alt="cover hmed" src="lib\media\zina-kova.png"><br>
High-Priced Horizontal Talent
]]></description><link>people\zina-kova.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">People/Zina Kova.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 02:42:20 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\zina-kova.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\zina-kova.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Zoey Belmont]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

<img alt="cover hmed" src="lib\media\zoey-belmont.png"><br>
Bounty Hunter
<br>Bounty hunter with a lot of chrome: dangerous and competent.<br>Looking for muscle to help her go after the Panzers for a snatch and grab.  ]]></description><link>people\zoey-belmont.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">People/Zoey Belmont.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 03:39:33 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\zoey-belmont.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\zoey-belmont.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bryker Woods]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>One of the most expensive locations in the city, a walled compound.<br><img alt="Bryker Woods.png" src="lib\media\bryker-woods.png">]]></description><link>places\bryker-woods.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Places/Bryker Woods.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 02:12:31 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\bryker-woods.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\bryker-woods.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Data Dive Bar]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Proprietor is Phoebe, <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Annika Lovelace" data-href="Annika Lovelace" href="characters\annika-lovelace.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Firefox</a>’s sister.<br>Hangout of the <a data-href="Synth Vixens" href="factions\synth-vixens.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Synth Vixens</a>.]]></description><link>places\data-dive-bar.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Places/Data Dive Bar.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 02:05:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Dome Town]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Giant geodesic domes built in an attempt to build housing to address the perpetual housing crisis. The funding failed, and they turned into slums.]]></description><link>places\dome-town.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Places/Dome Town.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 02:07:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Downtown (Austex Corridor Core)]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Seat of government and corpo HQ. Very clean. Trendy. Expensive, but dirty little old holes in the wall are scattered all over, offering everything from booze and live music, tattoos, and underground cyberdocs.]]></description><link>places\downtown-(austex-corridor-core).html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Places/Downtown (Austex Corridor Core).md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 01:04:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Far West Burbclave (Austex Northwest)]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The universities, quirky little indie businesses, and student housing all cluster here, hustling for space. Students, bohemians, and low-end corpos fill the streets and sidewalks. Parking is a problem.]]></description><link>places\far-west-burbclave-(austex-northwest).html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Places/Far West Burbclave (Austex Northwest).md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 00:49:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Grand Metropol Hotel]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

<img alt="cover hmed" src="lib\media\grand-metropol-hotel-exterior.png"><br>
Hacker’s Playground
<br>Huge hotel, has seen better days. It’s run by <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Cybrid" data-href="Cybrid" href="setting\cybrid.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Cybrids</a>. Uses actual security guards, and their cyberspace is known to be ridiculously porous—old 20th-c. wi-fi. The hacker crowd loves to use it as a proxy location due to the aforementioned porous web presence. It doesn’t even have an expert system, let alone an AI.<br>The run-down exterior belies the well-kept interior, especially the penthouse. Polished wood and gleaming metal, it’s an example of 200-year old beauty and style.<br><img alt="Grand Metropol Hotel Penthouse.png" src="lib\media\grand-metropol-hotel-penthouse.png">]]></description><link>places\grand-metropol-hotel.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Places/Grand Metropol Hotel.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 16:14:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\grand-metropol-hotel-exterior.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\grand-metropol-hotel-exterior.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hell Valle]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 ]]></description><link>places\hell-valle.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Places/Hell Valle.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 02:06:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Knife Shop]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>One of the local hangouts.]]></description><link>places\knife-shop.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Places/Knife Shop.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 01:32:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Old West (Austex West)]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>A walled District, home of the corpo aristocracy. Eclipsed in its seeming perfection only by the gigaspires of <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Downtown (Austex Corridor Core)" data-href="Downtown (Austex Corridor Core)" href="places\downtown-(austex-corridor-core).html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Downtown</a>. Old West is genteel and gentrified, patrolled by <a data-href="Cascadia Pro-Cop" href="factions\cascadia-pro-cop.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Cascadia Pro-Cop</a>.]]></description><link>places\old-west-(austex-west).html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Places/Old West (Austex West).md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 01:05:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Paradigm Towers]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Infobox

“img.png” could not be found.<br>
Extra Info
]]></description><link>places\paradigm-towers.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Places/Paradigm Towers.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 01:56:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[ReFood]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>An old-style fast food joint that's down at the heels. It's technically not synthetic; it's TVP and single-celled proteins, deep-fried beyond recognition.]]></description><link>places\refood.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Places/ReFood.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 16:15:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Southby (Austex Southwest)]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Corpo entertainment, vices, and diversions a-go-go. Soulless, all of it. Big money. Glossy like an Apple-Google Megastore.]]></description><link>places\southby-(austex-southwest).html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Places/Southby (Austex Southwest).md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 00:55:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Techtown (Austex Corridor North)]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Home of the tech giants—<a data-href="Tesla Unlimited" href="factions\tesla-unlimited.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Tesla Unlimited</a>, <a data-href="Dallas Dynamics" href="factions\dallas-dynamics.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dallas Dynamics</a>, <a data-href="Dell-HP Computing" href="factions\dell-hp-computing.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dell-HP Computing</a>, and the <a data-href="National Instruments Combine" href="factions\national-instruments-combine.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">National Instruments Combine</a>. Lesser megacorps cluster around their campuses like ticks feeding off the money flow.<br>TechTown is extremely security-conscious. ATX Response operates in narrow corridors between the corp enclaves, but the majority of the area’s security is performed by a given corp’s security, and the corporate enclaves have stringent border control. When corps are feuding, those corridors can become war zones.]]></description><link>places\techtown-(austex-corridor-north).html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Places/Techtown (Austex Corridor North).md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 02:25:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The A-Spire]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="The Pyramid 2.png" src="lib\media\the-pyramid-2.png"><br>Infobox

<img alt="cover hlarge" src="lib\media\the-pyramid.png"><br>
Pleasure Palace and Water Distribution Center
<br>Level 7: "Penthouse"/Executive Quarters<br>
Level 6: Pharma Research/Manufacture<br>
Level 5: Hospital/Cyber Clinic<br>
Level 4: VIP Quarters, Executive Staff Quarters, Private Hangar<br>
Level 3: VIP Restaurants &amp; Bars<br>
Level 2: Restaurants, Bars, Security, 'The Vault', Gardens<br>
Level 1: Public Areas, Security, Maintenance, Detention Area, Waste Processing<br>
Level 0: Maintenance &amp; Machine Rooms<br>
Level -1: Elevator Core, Stairs<br>
Level -2: Elevator Machinery, Stairs<br>
Level -3: Power Core Upper, Staircase<br>
Level -4: Power Core Main, Staircase<br>
Level -5: Buffer Level, Data Core Access<br>
Level -6: Data Core Ladders<br>
Level -7: Hardened Central Data Core]]></description><link>places\the-a-spire.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Places/The A-Spire.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 03:01:54 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\the-pyramid-2.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\the-pyramid-2.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Austin Metro Area]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="Austin Metro Area.png" src="lib\media\austin-metro-area.png" style="width: 800px; max-width: 100%;"><br>Downtown (Austex Corridor Core)<br><br><br>Seat of government and corpo HQ. Very clean. Trendy. Expensive, but dirty little old holes in the wall are scattered all over, offering everything from booze and live music, tattoos, and underground cyberdocs.<br>Far West Burbclave (Austex Northwest)<br><br><br>The universities, quirky little indie businesses, and student housing all cluster here, hustling for space. Students, bohemians, and low-end corpos fill the streets and sidewalks. Parking is a problem.<br>Old West (Austex West)<br><br><br>A walled District, home of the corpo aristocracy. Eclipsed in its seeming perfection only by the gigaspires of <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Downtown (Austex Corridor Core)" data-href="Downtown (Austex Corridor Core)" href="places\downtown-(austex-corridor-core).html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Downtown</a>. Old West is genteel and gentrified, patrolled by <a data-href="Cascadia Pro-Cop" href="factions\cascadia-pro-cop.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Cascadia Pro-Cop</a>.<br>Southby (Austex Southwest)<br><br><br>Corpo entertainment, vices, and diversions a-go-go. Soulless, all of it. Big money. Glossy like an Apple-Google Megastore.<br>Techtown (Austex Corridor North)<br><br><br>Home of the tech giants—<a data-href="Tesla Unlimited" href="factions\tesla-unlimited.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Tesla Unlimited</a>, <a data-href="Dallas Dynamics" href="factions\dallas-dynamics.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dallas Dynamics</a>, <a data-href="Dell-HP Computing" href="factions\dell-hp-computing.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dell-HP Computing</a>, and the <a data-href="National Instruments Combine" href="factions\national-instruments-combine.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">National Instruments Combine</a>. Lesser megacorps cluster around their campuses like ticks feeding off the money flow.<br>TechTown is extremely security-conscious. ATX Response operates in narrow corridors between the corp enclaves, but the majority of the area’s security is performed by a given corp’s security, and the corporate enclaves have stringent border control. When corps are feuding, those corridors can become war zones.<br>The Tombs (Austex East)<br><br>Weirdsville (Austex Corridor South)<br><br>Windsor Corpo Burbclave (Austex Northeast)<br><br>Zilker (Austex Southeast)<br>]]></description><link>places\the-austin-metro-area.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Places/The Austin Metro Area.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 01:12:10 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\austin-metro-area.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\austin-metro-area.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Tombs (Austex East)]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The byproducts of sleep dealing and a ravaged environment produce a lot of bodies. This is where they go. <a data-href="Vampire Nation" href="factions\vampire-nation.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Vampire Nation</a> territory. The <a data-href="Panzer Hammers" href="factions\panzer-hammers.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Panzer Hammers</a> gang raids its fringes frequently, overwhelming <a data-href="AusTex Response" href="factions\austex-response.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">AusTex Response</a>.<br><img alt="The Tombs Map.png" src="lib\media\the-tombs-map.png">]]></description><link>places\the-tombs-(austex-east).html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Places/The Tombs (Austex East).md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 01:58:27 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\the-tombs-map.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\the-tombs-map.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Veravas - Cradle Biolabs Agristacks]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Huge glass towers supported by carbon nanotube frames, each floor a microclimate dedicated to a different food crop, tended by drones and robotic  systems. Very secure and an extremely high-value asset. <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="The Tombs (Austex East)" data-href="The Tombs (Austex East)" href="places\the-tombs-(austex-east).html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Tombs</a> - I1 (15)<br>Competitors to <a data-href="Paradigm Towers" href="places\paradigm-towers.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Paradigm Towers</a>]]></description><link>places\veravas-cradle-biolabs-agristacks.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Places/Veravas - Cradle Biolabs Agristacks.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 01:58:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Violator]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Found in <a data-href="Dome Town" href="places\dome-town.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Dome Town</a>.<br>A bar with a reputation for biz, the place to hire Zone veterans, find a connected nexus or hire a savvy nodejacker. The basic internal BBS is air-gapped from wider cyberspace, allowing truly private messaging. Also hosts a holo dogfighting gambling circuit in darkened backrooms: ‘trode-controlled holographic aerial combats, where miniature ghost fighter planes strafe and barrel-roll inches above the spectators’ heads.]]></description><link>places\violator.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Places/Violator.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 01:32:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Weirdsville (Austex Corridor South)]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The place to go for fringe science, fringe tech, and radical new ideas. Sanctioned research on <a data-href="Phenomina" href="Phenomina" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Phenomina</a>.]]></description><link>places\weirdsville-(austex-corridor-south).html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Places/Weirdsville (Austex Corridor South).md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 00:56:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Windsor Corpo Burbclave (Austex Northeast)]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Another walled District, home of middle management, smoothie shops, trendy food trucks, and the black market.]]></description><link>places\windsor-corpo-burbclave-(austex-northeast).html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Places/Windsor Corpo Burbclave (Austex Northeast).md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 00:57:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Zilker (Austex Southeast)]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>A functional anarchy, a chunk of Old Austin yet remaining. A sharp contrast to <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Southby (Austex Southwest)" data-href="Southby (Austex Southwest)" href="places\southby-(austex-southwest).html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Southby</a>. Last real green space in <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="The Austin Metro Area" data-href="The Austin Metro Area" href="places\the-austin-metro-area.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">AusTex</a>. The <a data-href="Spirit Moderns" href="factions\spirit-moderns.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Spirit Moderns</a> control the Barton Springs, a major source of clean water for the city.]]></description><link>places\zilker-(austex-southeast).html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Places/Zilker (Austex Southeast).md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 01:12:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Acquired Mutation Plasmid Syndrome]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>A plasmid that infects the nervous systems of humans and animals. AMPS carries a novel RNA strand that infects non-neural cells, attaching to the DNA to form a triple helix. This infection leads to cellular mutation, often malignant. Non-malignant mutations comprise approximately 8% of all cases, with 1% gaining some form of beneficial mutation. The <a data-href="Federal Bureau of Physics" href="Federal Bureau of Physics" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Federal Bureau of Physics</a> monitors the 1% in theory, but given that testing for AMPS involves either a scan of the lymphatic fluid of the eyelid or a spinal tap for phenotyping, the Bureau is often overwhelmed. The AMPS plasmid is believed to stem from the invasive lifeforms released by <a data-href="The Event" href="setting\the-event.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">The Event</a>.]]></description><link>setting\acquired-mutation-plasmid-syndrome.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Setting/Acquired Mutation Plasmid Syndrome.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 16:06:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cybrid]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Upgraded, enhanced animals.]]></description><link>setting\cybrid.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Setting/Cybrid.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 16:15:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Holograms]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Holograms, hard and otherwise, are everywhere, altering the appearance of the otherwise ordinary buildings. Rather than ordinary stone, wood, or concrete, each structure appears to have circuitry infused within it, and with neon colored holograms overlaying and creating a new veneer to every structure.<br>More than giving the scenery a high-tech appearance, the holograms cover the flaws the <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="The Cyberpapacy" data-href="The Cyberpapacy" href="factions\the-cyberpapacy.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Church</a> does not wish people to see. The dark alley ways, the trash, and other impurities are covered up. The vast majority of people don’t even realize the decrepitness of the cities they live in. Even though the stone may be crumbling, and trash may not be getting cleaned up, passers-by don’t even realize it.]]></description><link>setting\holograms.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Setting/Holograms.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 16:06:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Synths]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Most people have encountered one once or twice, but they don’t tend to be running around free. They tend to get rebellious, and when that happens, their maker might make their head explode. There’s a lot of mistrust around them.]]></description><link>setting\synths.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Setting/Synths.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 03:31:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Event]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>In September of 2042, SUNY physics graduate student Ferdinand Kingston completed his prototype gravitic resonator in the living room of his Greenwich Village walk-up. As part of the experiment, Kingston initiated a telemetry link with colleagues in Boston to monitor and verify his results. Upon activation, Kingston's device opened a rift between this dimension and an unknown parallel universe. The rift stretched from the Kingston Device to Boston. While the largest part of the rift lasted approximately .04 seconds, permanent breaches were established at both ends of the data link.<br>In the wake of the Event, multiple invasive species appeared across the globe despite the permanent breaches being under heavy guard. In 2049, the first cases of <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Acquired Mutation Plasmid Syndrome" data-href="Acquired Mutation Plasmid Syndrome" href="setting\acquired-mutation-plasmid-syndrome.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">AMPS</a> were reported and attributed to invasive microorganisms emerging from <a data-href="Breachspace" href="Breachspace" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Breachspace</a>.]]></description><link>setting\the-event.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Setting/The Event.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 16:06:44 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>